Don't try to remember.
He doesn't
think anything of me.
So I'm not going to see him anymore.
You're back, Daughter.
Dad.
I told you to stop calling me that.
It creeps me out.
Sorry about that, Nino.
I just received word that
you all passed the exams.
The six of you managed to pull it off.
Congratulations.
Th-Thanks.
It seems I have no choice but
to approve of Uesugi.
So from tomorrow on,
he can come here too—
I'm not going to see him anymore.
Also, we've decided to stay at
our new place for a while longer.
What did you say?
We're not going to make Ichika
do all the work, of course.
I'm going to get a job, too.
I'm not going to pretend we've
become independent or anything.
I know we're not doing
the right thing, either.
But I have a feeling that
living like that will change us.
I feel like we've made some progress.
I fail to understand.
Abstract ideas like "progress"
couldn't be less convincing.
I've seen your so-called new home.
To me, it looks like you've gone backwards.
You mustn't have forgotten
in just five years.
You don't want to live
like that anymore, do you?
Stop being selfish and...
What?
There you are, Nino.
We're going back.
Wh-What is that?!
Hurry up and get on.
We need to get back before work.
Nino.
The path you're about to walk is a thorny one.
It won't end well.
You're certainly going to regret it.
Come with me.
Dad, just watch us.
Go.
Erm...
U-Uh...
I'll be taking your daughter, sir.
Ebata.
It seems, happily, that my daughters
have all passed the exams.
Am I smiling like I should?
Of course, sir.
I see.
Of course I am. I am their father, after all.
I thought I told you I was done with you.
It seems that relationships
require mutual input, unfortunately.
Huh? What?
And where did you get this bike?
I borrowed it from my boss.
I told you, I used to do deliveries.
That's when I got my license.
I see.
You look shockingly tacky with it.
Aren't these your exam results?
No! Don't look at that!
I bet it turns out that you
got 100 in all subjects.
You...
Biggest failure of my life.
I'm seriously embarrassed.
Is this our fault?
It isn't.
Never mind that. I'm going to floor it.
Hang on tight.
My long job as a tutor
has come to a close today.
Nino's right. I'm not needed anymore.
This is the end of our relationship too.
I'll miss it. Won't you?
You're going so slow!
I thought you were going to floor it.
What do you expect?
I'm carrying a lot of weight.
Huh? Who are you calling heavy?!
Jeez, you drive me crazy.
You've always been like this.
A jerk of the highest order.
And, also...
I love you.
Uesugi!
You brought Nino back?
We're over here.
Okay.
I said it!
I went and said it!
What's gotten into me?
Liking someone like him?!
That was my first confession!
Why did I do it?
What do I do?
And why isn't he reacting at all?
Cheers!
Congratulations on making it
through the finals.
I can't believe we pulled it off.
I know.
I want to frame our exam papers.
Why don't we do that when
we get slightly better grades?
I know we're celebrating,
but can we really afford all this?
The owner is treating us to celebrate.
Remember to give us five stars.
Our orders are all over
the place, aren't they?
I guess this is business as usual for us.
Here, Yotsuba.
Huh?
What's this for?
Your predictions on the contemporary
literature questions were spot on.
They were.
That really helped.
Me too, then.
Me too. Me too.
Okay, then...
It's so good.
You all helped me out too, though.
I have to return the favor.
We do too, actually.
Why don't we all share a little, then?
That's how we made it
through the exams, after all.
Plus, this way, we can enjoy
all the different flavors.
That's your real motivation, isn't it?
Here, Ichika.
Thanks.
And congratulations.
I never would have thought
you'd do the best, Ichika.
I got lucky. That's all.
I'm beating you next time.
Yeah.
I'm going to take a short break.
You can handle it from here.
Oh, boss, is it all right
if I set aside some pudding?
Sure, but did you ever like pudding?
No, it's in return for a Valentine's Day gift.
I thought you were one of us!
Traitor!
Uh, it was from my sister.
Here you go!
Oh, that's what it was.
I thought it was from one of the five girls.
That would never happen.
Actually, I've been getting some
all the time since January.
Nah, no way.
Working hard, huh?
Wh-Where's the boss?
He just went into the back.
Oh, okay.
I was going to thank him.
I guess I'll wait for a bit.
I hope I hid it well.
It's true that I was rooting
for Miku... I think.
But just for a moment...
Miku said she'd confess if she came in first.
But I had the highest grade this time.
Does that mean I can?
Thanks for helping with the dishes.
It's in return for the treat.
You can go now.
I'll let the boss know.
Go have a seat.
R-Right.
I'll do that.
What's wrong?
Forget what I said on the bike.
I'm sure I troubled you with what I said.
It was so sudden.
I think I went too fast.
What am I doing?
Nino...
What are you talking about?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
It was so windy. I might have missed it.
What the hell?!
No, I mean, what?
Never mind!
I guess he never heard me.
We aren't girlfriend material to him anyway.
He never even noticed when Miku gave
him Valentine's Day chocolates.
I'm actually glad he didn't hear me.
What was that about?
Boss, I'm done cleaning up.
I said I love you.
Huh? What?
I'm not asking for a response.
You're so frustrating.
If you don't see me as girlfriend material,
I'll force you to see me that way.
Remember how I said there's gotta be
at least one girl on this planet
who'd fall for a guy like you?
That girl is me.
Too bad for you!
F-Futaro.
Hey.
What a coincidence.
Are you shopping, too?
Yeah. It's my turn today.
Weren't there some shops
closer to your place? Why...
It's not like I took a detour to come
to this shop in order to have a chance
to run into you based on what I remembered.
I was just walking when I naturally
found myself at this shop.
The longest tale in Miku history.
Um...
Oh.
This.
I came for this.
Huh?
I never knew about this.
Y-Yeah.
This is the only place that does it.
This hot spring is near
where our Grandpa lives.
You can't even trade hot
spring vouchers for money.
The best prize is obviously
Prize E, the gift coupons.
Wait...
How much would Prize B fetch if you sold it?
I have a feeling you would
never win it, Futaro.
We won't know until we try!
Let's go pay.
Wait.
There's something Nino wanted me to buy her.
I-I see.
Has Nino said anything?
Like what?
No, right?
Never mind.
Hey, Miku...
Is there anyone you have
a crush on or anything?
There isn't.
I already told you that.
There isn't anyone in class that
you've since developed feelings for?
Let's talk about dating! Dating!
What's gotten into you, Futaro?
Um...
An acquaintance of mine apparently
got confessed to by a classmate.
Yeah?
They said they don't need
a response, but, uh...
Honestly, it's troubling.
What?
I didn't think you'd be one to
think about that kind of thing.
You're like a normal guy.
I'm just asking for someone I know.
I thought you'd be the type
to dismiss that kind of thing.
I'm glad.
What happened to my acquaintance was...
She tried to confess, but she didn't
have the guts to, apparently.
Once you do, you can't go back
to how things were before.
So it takes a lot of courage.
I see.
But...
I guess some people have that courage.
I don't know how to face her anymore.
Why am I such a coward?
Either way, it's spring break.
There's plenty of time to think.
Spring break...
Whoo-hoo!
!ooh-oohW
Traveling is the best.
This is all thanks to Futaro.
Thank you!
I can't believe I actually won.
What is this?
"The foremost tourist attraction
in the area: the Bell of Vows."
It says, "Any man and woman who ring
this bell together are forever bound."
Bro! Take a picture!
Okay.
Shoot, I forgot to charge it.
Come on!
Oh, well.
Let's move on.
Come with us, brother.
Yeah.
I'll forget about those girls
and enjoy this family vacation.
All right.
Whoo-hoo!
!ooh-oohW
Uesugi?!
Why are you here?
You're so fast, Itsuki.
Wait, what?
It's Uesugi!
No way.
You won, too, Futaro?
You guys are all here on
a family vacation, too?
This is insane.
Indeed, a family vacation.
But you must be careful.
You always have to expect something
to go wrong when you're traveling.
Now, then...
Shall we have lunch?
Begin preparations, everyone.
When did those girls work
things out with their dad?
What's the matter?
N-Nino!
What?
If you have something to say, say it.
Futaro.
W-Wait...
The way you said his name, "Futaro"...
What's wrong, Nino?
Huh?
It's been half a year
since we met each other.
It's about time we get
a bit closer, isn't it?
Well...
I do agree with that, but...
Oh, I know.
How about nicknames?
Miku, think of something.
Me?
Ue...
Fu...
Fu-ta.
Fu.
Nah.
Hey, that's not bad.
Never mind that, let's get ready for lunch.
All right, fine.
Hey!
Yotsu—
I'm getting nervous.
I don't know if I can do it right.
Ichika, could you explain something to me?
Sorry, I'm in the middle
of something. Maybe later.
What is this?
We've only been apart for a short while,
and they're all being distant.
Itsuki...
Itsuki, what are you doing?
Go retrieve our lunch boxes from Ebata.
Okay.
U-Um...
About the other day...
Now, then, let's prepare.
All of us are together for once.
I'm spending quality time
with my family, privately.
See you, Futaro.
We're probably at the same hotel.
Uesugi.
I need to speak with you later.
It's like a haunted house.
They're open, right?
When is "later"?
Maybe I should try calling.
Damn it!
She was around here...
When did she get up there?
Where did Itsuki go?
What?!
I'm in heaven.
Good thing there's a mixed bath.
The whole family can be together.
You shouldn't stay in for too long.
Right.
She said she wanted to talk...
What is going on?
This is Itsuki, right?
Why is she being so roundabout?
Th-The courtyard is this way, right?
Is he dead or something?
Itsuki.
There you are.
I was going to the courtyard.
What did you want to talk about?
L-Let's just go to the courtyard...
No.
Tell me now.
I'm not letting you get away.
Um...
What is your understanding
of your relationship with us?
Huh?
Well, I mean...
You said we're p-partners or something.
No, we aren't partners anymore.
We aren't doing lessons very often
anymore, so I can't deny that.
But I've been hired to tutor
until you guys graduate.
Until then, as your tutor, I'll...
We're through with that.
Let's put an end to this relationship.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Tell me what's going on!
Ow.
Did your father tell you to do this?
Why would you say that now?
Old man...
I thought you were dead.
Huh? Say what?
Don't you dare lay a hand
on my granddaughter.
I'll kill you.
Screw this noise.
I want to go home.
Bro!
It's morning!
Wake up!
What?
Let me keep sleeping.
I'm going to sleep forever
and fly off into the future.
Jeez.
Hello?
My brother is flying off into the future.
Sorry to disappoint you, Itsuki.
Good morning!
Itsuki! What was that about yesterday?
That's what I'd like to ask you!
Why didn't you come to the courtyard?
Hey, what's going on?
Give me a second.
Let's meet up to talk.
I would love to, but we're being watched
carefully to make sure we don't see you.
I don't think I can get out.
There's a good place, then.
Demiglace.
H-Hamburg steak.
Okay, seems like you're
the real Itsuki this time.
Yesterday, I met you at the front desk,
and I was told to stop tutoring.
So that wasn't you, then, was it?
It wasn't.
It could only have been one of my sisters.
It's settled, then.
One of them is rejecting me.
Did any of them seem suspicious?
Why did they disguise themselves as you?
Oh, about that...
Wow.
We seem to bump into each
other in the bath a lot.
Nino?!
Why...
Since we're here together...
Want me to wash you or something?
H-Hang on a second!
Let me ask you one thing...
Who are you?
You aren't Itsuki...
Which means...
No, wait...
Jerk!
I worked up all my courage for nothing.
Screw him!
You were absolutely in the wrong there.
That's crazy.
You all look the same.
I don't think we're the same in every way.
We're able to tell ourselves
apart, after all.
I'm sure you could, too.
All you need is love!
Here we go again with your crazy theories.
I'm baffled, though.
Nino used to hate you so much.
What could have changed?
So that was Nino.
It's not just Nino.
Ichika, Miku, Yotsuba...
They've all been a bit weird
since spring break started.
I called you out last night
to ask about that.
Can you think of a reason?
I guess I wasn't just imagining things
when I noticed they've been acting odd.
I have no idea.
Our top priority is solving
the Fake Itsuki question.
Unless we can figure out what
she's really thinking,
I may really be fired as your tutor.
You're right.
Though, there is something
Fake Itsuki said that I agree with.
I don't know what she's after.
But we aren't partners working
toward the same goal anymore.
Our many days spent studying
for exams together,
going to the fireworks festival, school camp,
last year's end, and New Year's...
We've shared so much time together now.
Wouldn't you say we're friends at this point?
Let's see...
At the very most,
we're complete strangers.
You say that so unironically.
My family vacation's ruined.
Let's do this, then.
I'll hear you guys out.
"Scrambled Eggs."