There's no way he would like someone like me.
Why are you assuming you've lost?
You've already lost in spirit.
It's Ichika I'm up against.
She's cute and social,
and she's popular with the guys.
And she has the strength to
believe in her own dreams.
If I were a guy, I would choose her.
Besides, there's you, too.
Gee, thanks.
Not that I didn't already know that I'm cute.
That just makes him even more messed up
for not immediately going out with me.
How much courage does he think it took me?
You confessed?
You're amazing, Nino.
So you haven't yet, have you?
He'll never get it through his
thick skull unless you tell him.
You're right.
I said I'd do it if I scored
the highest on our exams.
Or if I could bake good bread.
I kept making up excuses to put it off.
It's not Ichika's fault or anyone else's.
I did this to myself.
Okay, then.
Go ahead and stay cooped up
like this forever.
Always moping like that...
You and I really are on completely
different wavelengths.
But still, I thought you were a rival.
You're no match for me? What?
You said we're rivals in love, didn't you?
You had no trouble admitting that I'm cute.
Seriously, think about it carefully.
We're quintuplets.
You're obviously cute, too.
Wait, don't you think
this is a bit too short?
You're the one who told me to cut it.
I know, but I've never
cut it this short before.
Don't worry.
You look cute.
Y-You'd better be right.
Yeah, you're cute.
Bye.
Nino, I'm sorry.
H-Hey, where are you taking me?
Just come with me.
What's gotten into you,
Miku?
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
I want you to hear Miku out.
So long as Futaro knows
that Miku likes him,
my lie doesn't make any sense.
I'm going to use everything I can.
This is the only way I can do it.
It's the only way I can win.
Where are we?
You've been here before, haven't you?
Yeah.
When I was in elementary school.
When you were in elementary school?
I still remember that day.
That day, I wandered around this area
with Rena, wherever she wanted to go.
There's no way I wouldn't have
enjoyed traveling with her,
after she said she needed me.
Before I knew it, the sun set,
and it was night.
And then what happened?
My teacher from school was
supposed to come pick me up.
I got to wait in an empty room
at the hotel Rena was staying at.
I think we played cards.
Now it's just a nice memory.
Was she...
Are we done?
I only figured I'd tell you because
you might be plotting something.
But I'm tired of that.
I'm done playing your little game, Miku.
No...
Ichika.
See, I knew it.
What timing.
It's safe to assume you were the Miku that
I met in the school hallway the other day.
Th-That wasn't me.
Why did you lie to me?
You must have figured it out.
That girl from six years ago was one of us.
Yeah.
It was me.
That was me.
Me.
We met six years ago.
I'm not lying.
Believe me.
Do you remember which good luck charm
we bought together six years ago?
Yeah, I still have it.
I'd never forget it.
You're lying, aren't you?
Sorry.
I can't trust you right now.
Let's go back before we catch a cold.
Man, didn't the weather forecast
say it was going to be clear?
Where have you been, Uesugi?
Oh, you know.
You were lost, weren't you?
Also, what's the plan tomorrow?
The shower's free now.
Sorry for taking it first.
My underwear's soaked, too.
Y-You can go next, then, Yotsuba.
Okay.
I'm glad I didn't go.
Wow, Itsuki.
You're really going all-in, huh?
Not gonna wear it?
N-No, I'm not.
I'm going to throw it out
since it's too much for me.
Ichika,
don't you have something to say to Miku?
Sorry, Ichika.
I'm coming in.
Are you all here?
Message for everyone.
We're assembling in the main hall
in thirty minutes.
Why are you delivering this?
I am a class rep.
You guys...
W-Washroom!
Are you still fighting?
Tell me what's going on.
No, we're, well...
Man, that was refreshing.
I-It's not a big deal, right?
Yeah, this is just another day for us.
O-Obviously, right?
All right, then.
Anyway, thirty minutes.
Apparently, we're deciding on our
elective itinerary for tomorrow, too.
Give it some thought.
Sorry for talking out of turn.
It's fine.
Making Fu worry is the last thing I want.
And you need to stop running away like that.
But...
Miku, you can't keep this up forever.
Guys, let's make things clear.
All of us are looking for a chance
to be alone with Futaro.
That's what I've been saying this whole time.
You too, Itsuki?
I can't deny it.
None of us are going to get what
we want if we keep this up.
I'm sure that's not anyone's wish.
Look who's talking.
You hear me out too, Yotsuba.
He's not here anymore, is he?
We have elective field trips on our last day.
We're choosing from one of five courses.
Why don't we each choose one of the five?
The only person who gets a chance
is the one who happens to be on
the same course as Futaro.
Let's leave it all to luck.
Agreed!
There won't be any hard feelings that way.
I don't like it.
Are really we really gonna do this
after all that scheming?
Are you happy with this?
It's only a one in five chance.
I don't know how to face
Futaro right now.
So I want my odds to be lower.
I think this is the best option.
We should have done this from the beginning.
Can we just point like usual?
I bet we'll all choose
something different anyway.
One, two...
Yo, Uesugi, which course
are we choosing tomorrow?
Let's go for E.
Course D people, over here.
What was Course D again?
You know, like, Honnouji Temple
and samurai graves and stuff.
The historical sites.
I don't care about that!
You should have checked.
You like Japanese history too,
huh, Ichika?
I have a tummy ache.
Course E, over here.
We're leaving now.
Students on Course E, we've arrived
at our destination, the Studio Park.
Actually, I want Course D.
Miku, can we trade?
Why did she decide she wanted
to switch courses with me?
Ichika was supposed to be the one here.
Where are we headed?
Hey, Nakano. We meet again.
She ran away again.
She probably hates you.
Miku, stop!
Are you all right?
Sorry.
Don't run away, Miku.
Not that I think this is enough
to make up for what I did...
You gotta watch where you're going.
I'm sorry, Nino, I just can't.
She's trying to run away again.
What do I do?
Would you like to try on samurai clothes?
Ichika! Why are you...
What about you, Nino?
I just called in sick so I
could keep an eye on those two.
You aren't here to mess
with her again, are you?
N-No!
I bailed with a stomachache, too.
I don't expect you to believe me.
Even if I can't be forgiven for what I did,
I want to make things right as much as
I can before the end of the last day.
I can't believe you're also here
to support Miku, Itsuki.
Yotsuba...
Are you sure you don't want to tell him
that you were the girl he met six years ago?
There's no reason to.
As long as I know.
Huh?
Ichika and Nino are here, too.
You two came, too?
I guess we're all here on Course E.
Sheesh.
Nobody's playing by the rules.
Those two guys are in the way.
I'll go deal with them.
Ichika, try to get Miku to wear
the samurai clothes while she's here.
G-Get her? How?
Hey, you're great at
impersonating Miku, aren't you?
You're so mean.
Excuse me.
May I try on the samurai clothes, too?
Maeda and Takeda are late as hell.
And Miku said she'd wait, but she's gone.
I guess she left.
Considering what happened on
the first day, I can't blame her.
Miku.
So you did get dressed, too, huh?
I wasn't planning to, but the staff
were weirdly enthusiastic about it.
I don't look weird, do I?
Y-You look good.
Wh-Where are your friends?
Th-They're taking forever.
I don't know what to do with them.
Uesugi! Are you really here?!
Lured them in good.
Looks like Ichika managed to do her part.
Huh...
They look good together.
Futaro!
Take a picture! It's going to go back down!
All right. Fine.
Don't go thinking I'm giving you to her.
S... Sorry.
Oh, dear.
She's drenched.
Like we were yesterday.
What is she going to do
about her underwear?
You told me to watch where I was going.
You should pay attention
to your surroundings, too.
I told you, I'm sorry.
I'll apologize to the staff.
You should get changed.
Yeah.
Before we knew it,
we were talking like normal again.
It's strange, given everything that happened.
It's like I stop worrying about silly things
when I'm with him.
Like the fact that I'm soaked
all the way down to my underwear.
This paper bag is from an underwear shop.
Who was it?
Maybe it was the staff.
I'll take them up on their offer.
Good thing you had that underwear, Itsuki!
Why, though?
I thought I might need it in an emergency!
Those guys are still gone...
Where are they?
What's wrong, Miku?
I-I'm exhausted.
Let's sit down for a bit.
There we go.
Sorry, I'm back now.
How are they doing?
I think things are going well.
What do we do now, Yotsuba?
I picked up Miku's bread,
but I left it back at the hotel.
What? B-Bread?
Don't worry.
I just need to hand this to Miku, right?
The last three days went by so quickly.
Yeah.
Although it was just two days for me.
But it's fine.
I got to spend the last day with you.
That's good enough for me.
Miku...
What's that?
Why is my bread here?
You baked that?
I did, but...
I'm hungry. I'm going to take one.
That's already...
Yum.
I seem to have a bad palate.
Honestly, I'm not confident I
can give you good feedback,
but I can, at least, appreciate your effort.
You must've worked so hard.
Yeah.
I worked really hard.
I handed it to her.
Sorry, Ichika.
I think I've been rooting for
the passive one the most
because I wanted everyone to be happy.
So I never realized how
you were really feeling.
So, sorry.
I keep getting apologized to.
I'm the one who needs to apologize the most.
My mom used to bake for me a lot.
When I was six.
She baked bread every day until she died.
I was reminded of that for some reason.
Your mom?
It was the kind of popular handmade bread
that they serve at small cafés and stuff.
My dad and I loved it.
Anyway, no point talking about me right now.
No.
I want you to tell me more.
I never knew any of this, even though
we've spent so much time together.
I've been so busy thinking about myself,
I didn't even try to learn.
I want to learn more.
Everything about you.
And I want you to know
everything about me, too.
Like that.
That spot's famous for being used as a
magistrate's office in period dramas.
I'm content just having
been able to see it today.
I'm sure you are. I know.
I love that big bridge we just crossed, too.
TV shows again?
Yeah.
Oh, and I love that, too.
And I love that.
I love this, too.
That's way too many.
Not that I didn't know.
And I love you...
I'm sorry, Miku.
I'm sorry I kept getting in your way.
Futaro, I'm sorry I kept lying.
But what I said...
I met this really interesting boy today.
And we bought all these
good luck charms together.
He's still in the main hall right now.
Hey.
You came.
I was bored, being all by myself.
Let's play something.
H-How about Sevens?
It was just for a short while.
But I'm sure I fell in love with you
because of that moment.
Futaro, you might
not believe me anymore,
but that moment...
That memory isn't a lie.
Ichika, you know...
When I saw them together,
I couldn't keep my cool.
Before I knew it, I'd jumped on him.
Nino.
I kind of get how you feel now.
If things had happened
at slightly different times,
our roles might've been reversed.
I'm sorry for being so condescending.
That's not true.
That's not true at all!
Thanks.
But at the same time,
I realized how stupid I am.
You must have, too.
Miku refused to hold anything
against you the whole time.
Going behind each other's backs,
dragging each other down...
We aren't getting anything
out of fighting each other.
We aren't enemies, are we?
Let's go apologize to Miku.
I'm sure we can be on even
better terms than before.
We get to talk about something
we all like, for once.
And I love you...
Yeah.
I know.
But...
Yeah.
I really do love my family.
Why are you here?!
You noticed, Miku?!
When?
I knew it.
I thought something was up since
I heard Ichika and Nino's voices.
Wait, let me walk through this...
Which means that "I love you" just now...
It was directed at my sisters hiding in there.
Did you think...
I was talking about you?
Y-You're just messing with me!
Are you sure about that, Miku?
You'd finally managed to tell him
how you feel.
It's fine.
I'm not like a certain someone
who's stupid enough to go charging in
when I don't even stand a chance.
Who are you calling stupid?
Besides, Futaro's not as dense as we think.
I should have known.
So, Yotsuba, thanks for the bread.
I was worried for a while.
Also, I think these are yours, right, Itsuki?
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Nino.
Don't bother. We're family.
Yeah.
Thanks.
And Ichi—
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Miku.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
I guess falling in love is painful.
Thanks, Ichika.
What they did and talked about from
then until it was time to meet up again
is something only they would know.
Futaro.
I caused you trouble, too.
Sorry.
Well, uh...
I went too far yesterday.
I didn't even listen to what you had to say.
I regret it.
That's exactly right.
You're the worst,
glaring at a girl like that.
Sorry.
I was so sad, you know.
I'm kidding.
It's all a lie.
All?
All of it.
Did you hear, Uesugi?
About that sneak photographer.
Sorry, I screwed up.
So it was you.
I tried too hard.
It's fine.
I was the one who asked you, after all.
Okay, say cheese.
Do you take the groom to be your wedded
husband, to have and to hold from this day on,
for better for worse, for richer for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
to love, cherish, and to obey,
till death do you part?
You may now kiss the bride.
Now I shouldn't have to worry about
being fooled by them anymore.
What the...
Uh, seriously, what the...
That was the day.
That must have been the day
that I started to feel she was special.
From that moment.