yorokobi mo
Happiness
happiness
kanashimi mo
Sadness
sadness
anata sae
Or even you
gotoubun nan desu
Are to be shared in fifths
hitotsu tsukuriwarai mo minukare
First: I can see through your fake smile
futatsu anta nanka daikirai yo
Second: I hate you
mittsu massugu na kono kimochi kizuite
Third: Notice these straightforward feelings
yootsu ki ga tsuku to dandan
Fourth: And when you notice
itsutsu wakariaeta ne
Fifth: We can understand each other
benkyou dake janakute kimi wo shiritai yo
We don't just want to study, we want to learn about you, too
daikirai kara
Hating one day
hating one day
daisuki e to
Loving the other day
loving the other day
kawaru kokoro ni tsuite ikenai yo
This changing heart can't be followed!
donna koto mo
Everything
everything
anata sae
Even you
even you
gotoubun desu
Are to be shared in fifths
demo watashi
But I
watashi
I
watashi wa
anata ga suki yo
love you
We are the brides!
We are the brides! We are the brides!
Please