One week until finals.
They averaged 20 percent on the first test.
And on the midterm, they averaged 26 percent.
At this rate, if nothing goes wrong, we'll make it!
That's right, if nothing goes wrong!
He's late.
Saturday is tutoring day.
Everyone's here and waiting. What is he doing?
Uesugi?!
He's dead!
He's sleeping like he's dead.
I've done it again.
I focus too hard on studying,
and before I know it, it's morning.
You were so late,
we started without you.
R-Right.
I'm going to have you all pass everything this time.
To that end, I've prepared this.
It's a problem set that covers all the areas we can expect to come up.
If we go through this,
we should have a fighting chance.
A-Actually, maybe we can skip tutoring today.
Please take your leave!
No running away!
Take them!
All this...
I don't believe it.
Were you up all night working on this?
Wh-What does it matter?
I can't make you guys do all the hard work.
I have to set an example.
An example...
Anyway, let's get started before anyone dips.
R-Right.
Let's go.
Let go, Miku!
Give it up, Nino.
You give up!
My favorite actor's on the variety show airing right now!
No.
There's a documentary on right now.
I can't miss the special today.
It stays off during study time.
I've been wondering...
Do those two not get along?
I'm not sure.
They're like a cat and dog, I guess.
Especially Nino.
Believe it or not, she's the most sensitive of all of us.
So she butts heads a lot.
Okay everyone, let's continue.
Well then, Futaro,
we'll be in your care for the next week.
Yeah. Time for a rematch.
Hey, that's my eraser.
I'm just borrowing it.
Oh, really?
Hey, that's my drink.
I'm just borrowing it.
Yuck!
I'm glad everyone's actually studying...
But now we have a new problem.
Ideas welcome.
Okay, how about this plan?
Operation Everyone-Gets-Along!
If you can get those two in a good mood, Uesugi,
they should stop fighting too.
Wow, amazing!
I'm impressed.
You two seem to be doing great.
You're both studying very hard and making amazing progress, and...
Yeah!
Attagirls!
He sucks at giving compliments!
What's gotten into you, Futaro?
You're creeping me out.
He's not creepy.
I'm just being honest.
You're going too far. Take it back.
What's that?
So you did think it was a little creepy.
Fail.
Next.
How about this?
Operation Third Force.
If you become their common enemy by being really hard on them,
it'll bring them together.
What's wrong?
They're trying the best they can.
I wouldn't feel good scolding them for it.
I didn't know you actually cared about people's feelings.
Oh, come on!
Is that all you've managed to do so far?
Well, not like finishing these problems will be enough for you halfwits!
Oh, I'm sorry, did I say halfwits?
I meant one-fifth wits!
Is it just me, or is he enjoying this?
So you say, but I'm almost done.
See?
Wait, this section's not going to be on the exam.
What?
Shoot!
Nino, take it seriously, please.
I would if I could, but this is too boring.
I'll study in my room. Leave me alone.
H-Hey!
An entire set's gone to waste now.
Hang in there.
Weren't you going to set an example?
We're counting on you.
Yeah.
Wait, Nino.
We've only just started.
Stick around for a while.
You're already off to a late start.
You gotta catch up with the others.
Shut up.
You don't know anything.
I don't have to take this from you.
You're just a tutor for hire.
You're an outsider.
Here.
Futaro made these for us.
Take it.
So what if he made some problem sets?
I don't need them!
H-Hey, calm down you two.
Yeah, guys.
Pick it up, Nino.
Wh...
Why are you getting fooled by these scraps of paper?
You showed up late today, too.
You half-ass everything.
If you think you're teaching us anything like this, you're sorely mistaken.
Nino...
Uh-oh.
Miku, don't worry about me.
Nino.
Apologize, now.
You owe him an apology.
Since when have you been on his side?
You fell right for his slick talk!
Getting all worked up over this trash!
It's not trash.
He doesn't have a printer or a photocopier, you know.
Can you believe him?
He actually handwrote all of it.
So what?
So the least we can do is take this just as seriously as he does.
It's not like I...
Nino...
Accept it already.
I get it.
You guys are going to choose him over me.
Fine.
I'll just move out, then.
Nino! Calm down!
I've been planning on it for a while now.
This place is ruining me.
N-Nino!
Mother would be so sad if she saw us now.
Don't do this!
Let her go already. And quit trying to act like her replacement all the time.
Nino, you need to think this through!
Yeah, let's talk it over.
She was the one who hit me first.
I can't live with that abusive monster of a sister.
A-Abusive... monster...
Oh, if I'm such a pain in the ass, I'll move out!
Oh, really? Fine, go.
Wh-What should I do?
Only the next day did I hear from Miku that Itsuki and Nino had actually left home.
Does this happen often?
We're sisters.
It's not uncommon.
But I feel like this time, it's a bit different.
Ichika and Yotsuba tried to talk sense into them,
but they're both being stubborn.
They're acting like if they come home first, they'll have lost.
Those idiots...
So, where are those two?
They said they had some stuff to take care of.
Probably work, in Ichika's case.
So the two of us are going to have to find Itsuki and Nino.
Let's do this, Futaro.
Yeah.
I'm beat.
Well, we are the weakest two of the group.
All right.
Have you seen anyone who looks like this?
Must be useful to be quintuplets, huh?
Huh?
I've seen a face like yours at the hotel I'm staying at.
That must be Nino!
Wh-Why are you here?!
How'd you even get in?!
I told them I forgot my keys in my room,
and they opened it for me.
So much for security!
Nino,
about yesterday...
Get out.
We're through now.
Nino, what's gotten into you?
You've always been the one who cared the most about your sisters and your home.
I told you to stop talking like you know everything.
Especially when this was all your fault!
You should never have come into our lives!
Give that back! It's mine!
Hey!
Kintaro...
We figured out where Nino is,
but Itsuki is nowhere to be found.
Not much we can do now.
Let's call it a night.
I'm sure Itsuki is at some luxury hotel somewhere, too.
Actually, about that...
She forgot her purse at home.
Seriously?
I'm home.
Welcome home, Big Brother.
This smell...
Curry, huh?
Yup.
We've already started eating.
I bet she's hungry, too.
Raiha,
may I have seconds?
Sure.
Th—
Thanks for having me.
Thanks for letting me use the bath first.
Well, Itsuki, what do you think of our huge bath?
Oh, it was very cram—cozy and relaxing.
I know, right?
Raiha, we're taking a bath next.
Okay!
Bathtime! Bathtime!
Um...
Why—
G-Go ahead.
Why are you here?
This is so awkward.
I know how Nino feels now.
Brother, can you bring the bedding out?
Oh, I'll do it.
Is she actually staying over?
Wait a second...
Dad's leaving for work soon.
Let's all sleep together tonight.
This can't go on.
What am I supposed to say?
Uesugi, are you awake?
Y-Yeah.
I'm up.
Sorry for barging in today.
And about yesterday.
There's something I have to talk to you about.
Let's go for a walk, shall we?
Hey, look.
The moon's so bright tonight.
Uh sure, I guess?
Sheesh.
You lack class.
I don't want a lecture on "class" from someone who practically drank that curry.
Seconds, please!
I-I couldn't help it!
I hadn't eaten all day.
You should go home tomorrow.
Miku's worried too.
I can't do that this time.
I can't go home until Nino apologizes.
Of course, I can't continue being a bother to your family, either.
By tomorrow...
You'll leave, and then what?
You have neither your wallet nor anywhere to go.
P-Please let me stay a little longer!
I'll do anything to help!
No way!
Go home!
Besides, I don't think a well off girl like you could survive in a place like mine.
I'm not well off.
We were living a similar lifestyle until just a few years ago.
Really?
Until our mother got remarried, to our current father,
we lived in extreme poverty.
Of course we did.
She had to raise five children all at once.
Nothing would make me happier than for you five to live in good health.
And our mother, who raised us all on her own, fell ill.
That's why I decided to guide the others in our mother's stead.
But it hasn't worked out as well as I'd planned.
So that must've been her doing what her mother would have.
You're trying to be a mother figure, huh?
Then...
I'll play the father.
Huh?
What do you mean?
I-I mean, what the hell is your father doing at a time like this?
Your dad should be stepping in here!
I'll just accept that this is also part of my job as your tutor.
That day, when I met that girl in Kyoto,
I decided that someday,
I'd become a guy who was needed by someone.
That's why I study.
But you? Our father?
Shut up.
Don't be picky.
The full moon sure is pretty tonight.
You still have a lot of studying to do.
Wh-What's that supposed to mean?
What's wrong?
I felt like someone was here just now.
D-Don't scare me like that!
Itsuki, go check it out!
What happened to playing the father?!
That's irrelevant right now!
Itsuki, I don't mind you going—
Don't talk to me out in public!
People are going to think we're walking to school together.
What a pain.
I don't mind you going to school from my place,
but what are you going to do about your textbooks?
Not to worry.
I bumped into Yotsuba yesterday and had her bring them to me.
Why didn't you ask for your purse, too?
I had the same thought later,
but Yotsuba seemed busy.
She wasn't at home yesterday either.
I wonder what she's up to.
Huh? You haven't heard?
You signed up to help the track team?!
Do you have any idea how dire things are?!
I'm sorry.
I turned them down once,
but they said they wouldn't be able make it into the marathon without me.
There you go again, being nice to everyone.
Go quit right now.
Stop causing more problems.
Sorry for keeping it a secret.
But I am working on your problem set when I'm at home.
Nakano, practice is about to resume.
Okay.
I'll do my best, okay?
We're not done talking here! You're not getting away!
She got away.
Nino!
You came to school?
I'm not bothered about what happened.
Just go home, okay?
You can get back on good terms with the others.
Just like old times.
Fine. I'll go home.
Really?
Not to the hotel from yesterday!
Nino!
Please, sir.
What are you going to do about the exams?!
Calm down.
We ask that you leave if you aren't a guest.
I'll make sure you pass!
So let me in!
So what if I pass the exam?
I don't care.
I'm not giving up...
I'm not giving up.
Nino!
Hear me out!
I'll be back!
I'm not giving up!
Four days until exams.
What can I do to get them back together?
If I drowned here, would they get worried and get back on the same page?
Whoa, my thoughts are going down a dangerous road.
But wait, maybe...
No, that wouldn't work.
It obviously wouldn't work.
I've been doing it wrong.
Maybe I had the wrong idea,
because they trusted me and were counting on me.
It wasn't my place to concern myself with another family's problems.
No, in fact...
You should never have come into our lives!
She's right.
It was all wrong from the beginning.
All I've been doing is studying.
I can't make myself useful.
They don't need me.
There you are, down in the dumps again.
You haven't changed, have you...
Futaro Uesugi?
It's been a while.
Uesugi?
What are you doing here?
Yotsuba?
U-Uh...
Sorry, I'm in the middle of practice.
Please take care of Nino and Itsuki for me.
Right.
Nino.
That's as far as you go.
He's back again!
Please, turn back.
How many times do we have to tell you?
Creep.
We're never going to let you in!
He'd better knock it off.
I need to tell him off.
How many times do I have to turn him away?
He just keeps coming back.
He doesn't know when to stop.
You're going to freak the other guests out if they see you walking around looking like a bum.
You're being a bother.
Come to my room.
"Seven Goodbyes, Part 2."