Everyone's ready.
Man, we have exams coming up,
and these girls couldn't
care less about studying.
Have you still not gotten in contact with Miku?
The number you called...
I think her phone's turned off.
Hang on. She told me where she went.
Ichika!
If Yotsuba can't say no,
you can say no for her.
You're good at impersonating
each other, are you not?
I'm not that good at it.
Remember what happened
when I tried to impersonate Ichika?
I know.
As soon as Miku arrives,
we'll have her wear your track suit, and—
Shoot!
They're leaving!
We need to act before
they get to the station!
But what do we do?
I'm not going home, no matter what.
You're going to make yourself sick
with all that sugar.
None of your business.
You drink old lady tea. You'd never understand.
You're such a child,
not appreciating this refined taste.
Leave once you're done drinking that.
How did you even find out
where my new hotel was?
I went to your last hotel the day before.
I saw you stomping out.
What were you doing with Futaro?
If I had to describe what happened
the day before yesterday in one word...
Terrible.
I'm never going to forgive that bastard.
Wh-What did he do to you?
Hear me out!
He showed up in disguise! He tricked me!
Oh.
That's it?!
He was horrible!
Why aren't you making more of a reaction?!
I mean, that's something we do all the time.
I mean, yeah, but...
That time,
and that time...
It was him all along!
I won't forgive him.
Is that all that happened?
That's it.
That's all it was.
Are you sure?
He also said he wanted
the five of us to stick together.
Exams and stuff aside.
Futaro said that?
He said that after I told him my situation.
Talk about selfish.
Don't you want to come home, Nino?
Why should I go home?
What's the point of sticking together
when we're all so far apart?
Because we're family.
Is that not enough?
I guess you think we've all changed,
but from my perspective,
you've changed a lot, too.
Changed? How?
You never used to drink black tea before.
That's it?!
We're all still one-fifth of a person,
scoring a twenty each.
Those problems...
Hey, I never said you could look!
You got question three wrong.
The answer is Battle of Nagashino.
What, are you trying to show off
because you studied?
No.
I've always liked Sengoku warlords.
Sengoku warlords?
Those old dudes?
Yeah.
This is my twenty.
And...
It's too sweet.
What are you doing?!
But I'd never have known what this
tastes like if you weren't around.
It's true that the five of us
used to be identical,
and we never got into arguments or trouble.
But we would have always stayed
at a twenty that way.
We should laugh, get angry, feel sad,
each experience life differently—
complementing each other where we fall short—
and grow into the people we're meant to be.
So it's all right that we're different.
By the way, with you gone,
the food at home is a disaster.
We don't have a balanced diet.
That's for you to figure out yourselves!
So bitter.
I never would have thought
to drink something like this.
Black tea's still better.
Black tea starts off bitter, too.
It's a classy kind of bitter.
It definitely comes from high-quality tea leaves.
The bitterness of green tea has depth.
I'm sure it uses better leaves.
Fine, I'll look it up.
Don't go crying if it turns out
that they use weeds for green tea.
Right back at you.
Black tea and green tea
use the same tea leaves.
The difference is the amount of fermentation?
Seriously?
I need to tell the rest of the gir...
I need to forget the past
and accept the present.
Maybe it's time to brace myself.
You'd best brace yourself, too, Miku.
I-I'd like to leave the team.
No!
Act stupider!
I can't!
I already want to quit this role!
That's it! That's it!
Itsuki, you're Yotsuba right now.
You, at least, look perfectly like her.
Are you sure this is going to work?
Groper!
There's a groper!
A groper?
Really? Was that him?
You there! Hold up!
Nakano!
Stop!
What a suicidal tactic...
I don't have a choice anymore.
He got away.
I can't go to training camp.
I'd like to leave the team.
Why?
Exams are coming up next week.
No, no.
What I mean is...
Why is someone pretending to be Nakano?
Huh?!
Gotcha!
I caught the groper!
This smell...
You're too heavy.
U-Uesugi?!
Why?!
Well, there you have it.
Why did you stoop to groping?
No, that's a lie!
I lied to lure you away!
Huh? Me? What for?
Itsuki is requesting your resignation
in your place.
Hey!
You can't go back now!
I'll be fine!
You have to stop...
Hide!
Something's not right.
I-I'm Yotsuba!
Look at this ribbon!
Yeah, you look alike, but you aren't her.
Your hair's not the right length.
Indeed!
What an astute observation!
This happened before, too!
You need to show more
interest in other people!
Thank you for worrying for me.
But I'm sorry, I'm going.
Hey, wait!
I'm back!
Sorry for the trouble, everyone.
Nakano!
That was just a prank.
A quintuplet joke.
Yotsuba...
Oh, I see, it was a joke.
Stop it. It's not funny.
Though, it's true that I want to quit.
N-Nakano... Why?
Why?
I mean, you have to be out of your mind to
start a training camp right before exams.
Seriously. Out of your mind.
R-Right...
What's going on?
I-It's happening...
That's my doppelganger!
Please don't kill me!
Doppelganger? You mean...
Oh!
I made it in time.
Ichika!
That was a close one. Thanks.
If you hadn't brought Miku...
I haven't done anything.
Miku!
Itsuki, Yotsuba, Ichika, Miku...
No...
When I arrived at the hotel, I saw Miku
standing there with a pair of scissors.
I don't know what exactly happened,
but she must have had a change of heart.
Right, Nino?
I can't believe you cut it so short.
Did you have your heart broken or something?
You could say that.
By who?!
Do you know, Miku?
What?
I don't.
Just so you know, it wasn't you.
R-Right.
Got it?
Goodbye, Kintaro.
And goodbye.
Yotsuba.
I just did as I was asked.
Are you happy?
We didn't have to do this.
I'm sure she would have understood
if you'd talked to her honestly.
You need to change, too.
It sucks, but it can't be all bad.
Yeah.
I'll go.
Want me to come with you?
Thanks, but I'll be all right by myself.
Nino, about the other day...
Stop.
Don't apologize.
You weren't wrong.
I was the one who was wrong.
Sorry.
Nino...
If you were wrong about anything,
it was how hard you hit me.
That really hurt.
Nino!
Oh, right...
I was going to give this to you
as a token of my apology.
Presale tickets for the movie
you said you wanted to see the other day.
Let's go watch it together.
Jeez, give me a break.
Why does nothing ever work out
the way you want it to?
I'm deeply sorry for the trouble I've caused.
I've spoken with the track team.
I'll help them with the meet,
and then part ways with them.
You're still hung up on that?
Hurry up and come in.
Okay!
Also, you two...
Welcome home.
We're back.
It looks like we've all finished our problem sets.
I don't know if we've leveled up at all.
Not to worry.
I have a plan.
The crib sheet!
I-I didn't think you'd be the kind of person.
What's the point of getting
good grades if we have to cheat?!
Then study up!
I'm whipping you into shape in the last two days
so you don't have to resort to this!
Prepare yourselves!
May I move forward with this plan?
What?
Why would you even ask
after how much you've done already?
I'll do it.
Thanks.
Let's get started.
Hurry up.
Okay.
I got all of the questions wrong.
You said you were smart,
but you're all talk, huh?
Why are you going out of your way for us?
I'm never having you teach me!
You should never have come into our lives!
Aren't you glad, Futaro?
Not yet. We're just getting started.
Today's the day.
I'm worried.
We did everything we could.
Right, Uesugi?
Huh?
Where's Uesugi?
He said he's calling Raiha.
Now?
It must be something urgent.
He even borrowed my phone,
because his phone's out of battery.
Good luck,
Ichika, Nino, Miku, Yotsuba, Itsuki.
The five of you together are unstoppable.
This is bad...
This is the best we could do
after how much we studied?
I guess we really are stupid.
Cheer up, Nino.
You need to worry about yourself.
Today happens to be tutoring day, too.
I guess we're going to spend today
reviewing the finals.
Speak of the devil.
Futaro's going to give us an earful.
I know.
Why do you sound so happy about it?
It's too bad we didn't do better,
but I can't wait to work with you guys again.
Huh?
It wasn't Uesugi.
Pardon me.
Oh, it's Mr. Ebata.
Are you not driving for Dad today?
I'm here today as your temporary tutor.
Y-You are?
He used to be a teacher, after all.
Is he skimping?
I wonder if he's sick or something.
Master Uesugi Futaro has quit tutoring.
I received word from your father, the other day
that Master Uesugi terminated his contract
as of the exam the other day.
Do you mean...
Futaro's not coming anymore?
No way...
It's because of how we did on the exam.
Dad said he would...
I don't believe that's the case.
I'm told that Master Uesugi resigned of his own accord.
Of his own accord?
Futaro... Why...
I can't accept this.
I'll call him over and talk to him myself.
I'm afraid that will not be possible.
Master Uesugi is forbidden from ever
setting foot into this home.
That is your father's order.
Why would he do that?
Fine.
I'll go.
Let me through, Ebata.
I cannot.
Though temporarily, I am
tasked with tutoring you.
I cannot let you go until
I teach you a certain amount.
We can go once we're done with this, right?
Yes.
Please feel free to.
These problems are relatively easy.
Ebata must be going easy on us.
Yeah.
I don't know if we could've
solved these in the past, though.
It's almost weird how easy the problems are.
I hate to admit it, but it's all thanks to him.
One more problem...
It's just one more problem.
I'm down to the last one, too.
I shall have to start a special lesson
if you aren't able to make it
through those problems.
Um...
Want to look at the crib sheet?
You mean the one from the final?
Yes.
We should all have it in our pencil cases.
A-Are you sure about this?
This is an emergency.
The ends will justify the means.
Itsuki looks like Uesugi!
You sure have changed.
I guess I will, too, then.
"Don't try to take shortcuts
to the answer, fools."
Look at that.
He never intended to let us cheat
from the beginning.
That sounds like Futaro, though.
What do we do now, though?
Wait, there's more.
"Two"?
Does he mean me?
"I'm not going to teach cheaters."
"You have to get there yourselves
from now on."
"I'm glad I'm finally done
with this hell job."
Itsuki?
"But it was a pretty fun hell. Later."
I still want Uesugi to teach me.
So do I.
I need Futaro.
But he can't come here anymore.
There's nothing we can do.
Guys, can I?
I have an idea.
Oh? What's the matter?
Mr. Ebata, please give us a hand.
You've grown up so much.
Merry Christmas!
Would you like to buy some cake?
Pardon me.
Yes?
It's you all!
Do you deliver cakes?
We'd like one delivered to our home.
What?
We don't do deliveries.
Uesugi.
I'll handle it from here.
You should go.
Wait, Boss!
I don't...
Uesugi.
Merry Christmas.
Hey.
This isn't the way to your place.
No, it's not.
This way.
Hey, I'm sorry I didn't tell you I was quitting.
But I can't go back to tutoring anymore.
Look at this.
This is our new tutor.
We wanted you to see this.
Y-Yeah? I'm glad it didn't take
too long to find a new one.
A graduate from a university
in Tokyo and a former teacher.
Huh.
He seems like he's up to the task.
Are you happy?
Are you really just going to leave us
with the next person and abandon us?
I had a second chance,
and I failed to produce results.
There's no guarantee
I'll do better on the next exam.
I had to give the job to a professional.
It's the right thing to do.
I can't let you suffer for
my selfish ends any more.
You're right.
You've always been selfish.
Thanks to that, we had to
study against our will.
We had to memorize and
learn formulas like crazy.
But we ended up happy when
we could solve problems.
It's all your fault that we made it this far!
You can't stop being selfish now!
Stop being reserved! It's creepy!
Sorry.
But I can't go back.
I quit.
I'm not even allowed to
go back into your home.
Is that a reason?
Yeah.
Let's just go already.
It's all right.
Thanks for the cake delivery.
No, I'm...
We're here.
This is our new home.
What do you mean?
We rented it.
I'm making a decent amount
of money, after all.
We're going to be living here from now on.
Now there's nothing in our way.
You're kidding me.
You let go of your place just for that?
Like we talked about before,
it's not where we are that matters.
It's that the five of us are together!
The apartment card keys!
Goodbye.
Shit.
I think you're someone who's needed now.
My life's flashing before my eyes.
It's been a while.
Isn't this all a little too recent, though?
If I drowned here...
Damn it, you all!
What good is it if we all jump in?!
Are you all right, Futaro?
Please don't give up after just two tries.
We can do it this time.
With you, we can.
Open that once you learn to accept yourself.
Nino! What's wrong?
It's too cold! I can't move!
Nino!
Can you get up?
Hang on.
You're all insane.
You need to think before you act.
I can't deal with idiots.
And I'm getting sick of
trying to be considerate.
I'm going to do as I please, too.
You'd better put up with my selfishness,
all the way to the end.
No...
This isn't what I think it is.
Since that's settled, let's go inside.
Is the cake safe?!
Don't worry.
Goodbye, Rena.
Come on, Futaro.
We're going to eat the cake without you.
All right.
Are you sure, though?
How are you going to split it
into five if I join?
"Good Work Today."