You fell into a pond?
No wonder you smell so bad.
You'd better use conditioner as well,
and not just shampoo. Got it?
Fine.
Damn it, what a pain.
I can't believe you put up with having such long hair.
Y-Yeah, well, I wash it every day.
I wonder if you could care for so much hair.
I'd never let it get that long in the first place.
I just imagined you with long hair, and now I feel sick.
I might look good.
Don't underestimate my potential.
Huh?
I just noticed I'm casually talking with Nino.
I don't even care about my hairstyle.
Then do something about your weird hair.
This is the only cut Raiha knows how to do.
I guess I have no trouble talking to her when it's just one-to-one.
Why are you making your family cut your hair?
Why don't you get your family to do yours, too? Maybe Yotsuba.
No way in hell.
Maybe I don't fully understand Nino yet.
Hey, what happened?
What happened before you came here?
Nothing.
Liar.
I've never seen you look so down before.
I-I wasn't down.
Just tell me.
I like being alone, but I get bored not having anyone to talk to.
Five years ago, I met a girl.
Futaro Uesugi.
It's been a while.
Are you....
The girl from Kyoto?
U-Um...
I'm glad you seem to be well.
Why are you running away?!
I can't meet you yet!
Why not?!
You're going to listen to me,
or you aren't getting this back.
That's cowardly!
Let's see...
How do I keep you from running away?
Hey, that looks perfect.
Let's ride that.
I don't know your name.
I'm Rena.
It's been five years, huh?
Rena...
Why are you here?
To meet you as you are now.
I heard you've been studying hard since then,
and that you're top of your class now.
And now you're a tutor, huh?
You're amazing.
You heard? From whom?
N-Never mind the small details.
What are your students like?
I don't know if you'd believe me,
but I'm teaching my classmates.
They're quintuplets.
Yeah?
I thought you'd be more surprised.
Oh, really?! I never realized quintuplets actually exist!
I've only seen them in TV shows!
The problem is that they're all idiots.
The eldest is an idiot chasing after a dream.
She doesn't expect it to work out,
but at least she has tenacity, I guess.
But she's stupid.
The second sister is a family-obsessed idiot.
She's really protective of her sisters, and she's quick to lash out.
And I thought that's all she was, but now, I don't really know.
But she's stupid.
The third is an idiot with self-esteem issues.
She was glum and listless when I first met her,
but she's been more vibrant lately.
So I'm relieved.
But she's stupid.
The fourth is a meatheaded idiot.
She's enthusiastic and dependable,
but she's the biggest source of my headaches.
Also...
No, I might be imagining it.
But she's stupid.
The youngest is a stuck-up idiot.
I don't get along with her.
She's capable, though.
I don't want her abilities to go to waste.
But she's stupid.
That about sums it up.
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
But I guess I'm surprised.
You're facing your problems head-on now, huh?
I think you're someone who's needed now.
Itsuki said the same thing to me.
You should never have come into our lives!
No...
I haven't changed at all since then.
Oh.
I guess I should probably get out of your life,
if I'm tying you down.
You can have this back, as I promised.
Thanks.
But I'm not giving this back.
What?
Why not?
Because I'm never going to see you again.
Never?
What are you talking about?
Hold on!
Please!
Open that once you learn to accept yourself.
Hey, wait up!
Goodbye.
And so she vanished.
The end.
Is she asleep?
Sorry to bore you with my story.
Why are you crying?
Y-You've liked her for five years now, haven't you?
That's so sad.
I-I never said I liked her.
I admired her and appreciated her. That's all.
That's what it means to like someone!
No, it's not.
Anyway, you don't need to feel so bad for me.
Well, that was a perfect sob story!
Just what I needed.
You're horrible.
You should cheer up, though.
I'm sure there's at least one person on this planet
who would fall for an insensitive guy like you.
Why are you out of the bath? You flasher!
We've seen each other naked already.
Forget about that!
What's this?
You've been working on these?
You picked out different problems for each of us, didn't you?
Deep down, I knew...
H-Honestly, I do feel bad about what happened.
Sorry.
Yeah, it's fine.
Go apologize to Itsuki now, too.
I'm not doing that.
Why not?!
Are you still pissed off about her slapping you?
She's never done that before.
I feel like I don't know her anymore.
Nino apologized?
I'm having a hard time believing that.
It's true.
You've gotta stop being so stubborn too.
Your hair's so shiny today.
What happened while you were with Nino?
A-Anyway, I know you two go out for lunch together and stuff.
I'm sure you can go back to being close, like-minded sisters once you cool off.
Nino and I aren't exactly like-minded.
Even when we went to the movies the other day...
Th-That was so scary.
It got boring after Ichika died.
That one in the trailers looked really good, though.
Oh, that one.
Origins of Life: Unknown Mysteries!
Love of Summer Vacation!
What?
That sounds lame.
No it doesn't!
You have bad taste.
So do you!
See?
Our tastes have drifted apart over the years.
I wouldn't want to see either of those movies.
I mean, still, though...
I have to prepare the garbage for tomorrow.
Tomorrow is non-combustible garbage day, right?
I'll take it out in the morning.
Thanks, Itsuki!
Huh? My watch...
It was just over there.
Itsuki, where do rubber bands go again?
They go with the combustible garbage.
Man, it's great having you around, Itsuki.
I'm starting to understand why you were so annoyed
when I was over at your place.
I'm going to call room service. Want anything?
A drink, then, please.
Okay.
I'll choose something for you.
Wait, why are you even here?!
What, not going to order?
You've got some nerve!
What happened to how reserved you were yesterday?!
Never mind that.
We have to deal with the problem at hand.
What problem?
Oh, the finals.
Oh, right.
I was here for the finals.
I made it through the day's quota!
Genius!
Genius.
We're almost done.
I wonder if Itsuki and Nino are studying right now.
We know where they are, right?
I'm sure they'll be back soon.
Do you think they're finally contacting us?
Sorry, it was from the captain of the track team.
I was honestly shocked by what happened yesterday.
I don't know why Rena showed up now,
but there's something she taught me.
You can't change the fact that people change.
You just have to forget the past and accept what comes.
So you should make up and go home.
"Forget the past"?
It's not that easy.
This is my room,
and I'm going to talk to myself.
Back when we used to look the same and had the same personality,
I felt like all of our thoughts were shared.
It was comfortable.
But that changed five years ago.
We all slowly drifted apart.
It was like they'd left the quintuplet nest and me behind with it.
I'm the only one who hasn't been able to move on.
I can't even change the length of my hair.
That's why I have to force myself to leave the nest.
Before I'm left all alone.
So this is what I'd failed to grasp.
This mindset of hers,
a result of how much she cares for her sisters.
Is that really what you want?
It is.
I have to forget the past and move on.
Other than that, if there's anything I regret,
it's camp school.
Kintaro.
Maybe it's because I never got to say goodbye.
I thought I might find some closure if I could see him again,
but he won't let me forget him.
What would you do if I said you could meet him?
Come in.
H-Hi.
Come in and make yourself at home.
Excuse me.
What do I have to do for Nino today?
A: Pretend to be make-believe man Kintaro,
and play along until she gets over him.
I'm over you!
B: Reveal everything and ask her to forgive me.
I forgive you!
The first option is the correct one if I'm thinking about the future, but...
Hey, Kintaro,
don't you have something to say to me?
It might not be that simple.
Right. There's something I have to tell you.
I'm sorry.
I'm actually...
It's all right.
I forgive you for standing me up on campfire night.
Although, that was just me aggressively telling you to come anyway.
No, I mean...
Okay, that's the end of that.
You can have this back.
You promised to hang out with me all day today, right?
You better not bail on me this time.
Actually, I...
Hang on, I'm concentrating.
I don't think now's the time to tell her who I am.
All right...
Let's get this done quick.
What are you making?
Sorry, I have to make a phone call.
Hello? Uesugi?
Kintaro's so nice!
And I get so nervous, I can't even look him in the eye.
Wh-What do you want?
Oh, sorry.
Kintaro doesn't hate cream puffs, does he?
I think he loves them.
Probably.
Okay.
I was thinking of making cream puffs.
Nice.
I love cream puffs.
N-No way.
I never thought you'd mess up with baking, Nino.
Huh?
Did you just...
Oh, Futaro told me you're good at cooking and stuff.
No, I mean...
Hey, he just called me by my first name!
Quit calling me over stupid crap!
Help yourself.
I made lots.
You sure did.
We have so many.
Let's call your sisters over to help finish them.
Please don't say that.
We're finally alone together.
I don't want them to get in the way.
I only want you here with me.
You're definitely cousins.
Uesugi said the same thing, too.
I get that I'm causing him a lot of trouble, messing up his tutoring and stuff...
That's not it.
Of course it is. All he ever talks about is studying.
I don't care about the exams!
I just want the five of you to be together!
I have something important to tell you.
I... Kintaro...
Hang on.
I have a feeling this is going to be long-winded.
Can I go to the bathroom first?
Huh?
Fine.
What is it?
Are you by the hotel?
I guess you could say that.
Come to the café on the first floor. Now.
What's the matter?
Why are you drenched in sweat?
Iced coffee is fine, right?
Yeah.
I think he might be about to ask me out.
Uh-huh.
I mean, he looked all serious,
and he said he has something important to tell me.
Hey, Kintaro!
Kidding.
He's obviously not here.
I know, right?
I appreciate you letting me see him.
Come on.
This isn't like you.
Whatever happens going forward,
I'm going to find a conclusion to my current relationship with him.
Nino...
Sorry I can't do anything.
Good luck.
I knew it.
I... Let me...
I told you, you'd better not break your promise.
You didn't...
I'm obviously going to see through your disguise.
You aren't twins, after all.
Bye-bye.
Nino! Open up! Please!
Can I help you?
The customer here just checked out.
It's morning.
Wake up, Itsuki.
Just a little longer.
We're leaving early today.
Give me five more minutes.
No. Get up.
Why not, Nino?
U-Um...
Good morning.
Yeah.
Nino?
I heard she's taking the day off.
What?
I thought so.
Let's go see Nino directly.
Sadly, that won't work anymore, either.
Believe in her and wait.
That's all I can do right now.
You've been weird all day today.
Did something happen?
It's nothing.
Let's go.
We have to go find the other problem child.
It's all thanks to you that we made it into the marathon.
We're all counting on the gifted runner, Nakano.
You? Gifted? The end times must be nigh.
U-Uesugi?
Who are you?
Are you the captain?
You're quite impressive, practicing for a meet when we have finals coming up.
Yup.
It's an important meet.
We don't have time to care about exams.
What?
"To care about exams"?
Don't worry! I'm working on it!
Yotsuba, you aren't pushing yourself too hard, are you?
No, it's all good.
Well, if you say so, I won't stop you.
I'll run with you.
I won't be interrupting, then, will I?
Five more laps!
I'm dying...
Uesugi, you should stop.
Not yet.
Which palace did Louis XIV of France build?
Berlin Palace.
Who's the author of Run, Melos!?
Dazai Ryunosuke.
What's the fourth element on the periodic table?
Hydro...
Lithio...
Barium!
They're all slightly off!
But she's learned more than I expected.
Is she actually going to do both?
You can't overdo it.
You should go take a break.
I'll be fine.
We're doing a training camp this weekend.
I don't know about that.
I thought we were taking the weekend off.
Listen, first-years...
We aren't going to two-peat the meet with that kind of thinking.
Yes, ma'am.
Not sending it?
Ichika!
You're going to give me a heart attack.
I have to brush my teeth, too.
I'm going to gargle.
Hold on.
You were holding onto your toothbrush without actually brushing again.
Here, let me.
I'll do it for you.
I used to do this for you all the time.
I'm not a kid anymore, though.
Say "ahh."
So bitter!
This is my toothpaste.
This is what grown-up toothpaste tastes like.
I guess you're still too young for it.
Yotsuba can handle it, yo!
You may have grown big, but you haven't changed.
Look at that.
You're too stressed out. You have ulcers.
I'm not...
Shush.
You're always going to be my little sister,
no matter how much you grow up.
I wish you'd depend on me more.
Would it be bad if I said I wanted to quit the team?
You can quit if you want.
No, I can't.
I'd be causing trouble for the team.
Look what you made me say,
playing the big sister all of a sudden.
We're the same age, you know.
You're still a little girl as long as you're wearing underwear like this.
Put those away!
And definitely don't bring them out when Uesugi's around!
Okay.
Did you get that?
Yes, she wears little girl panties.
Good.
I'm going to see the track team tomorrow.
What about you?
Of course I'm going.
We're going to free Yotsuba.
Pardon me.
Am I ever going to get any privacy?
"Seven Goodbyes, Part 3."