Uesugi...
Huh?
Just you here, Itsuki?
Y-Yes!
Did you just put something in your bag?
Yes, I'm preparing for the school trip.
Yeah?
It's coming up, huh?
Things aren't so great
between us right now...
but hopefully the school trip
brings us back together.
You're right.
We can get back to how we were before.
Underwear, socks...
Are you bringing your own toothbrush?
Come on, Raiha.
We don't need to buy everything new.
You have money saved up from tutoring.
No one's going to blame you for
spending some of it on yourself.
But the sisters are going to hate you
if you cheaped out on their birthday.
Huh?
Their birthday's coming up?
It already happened.
I guess it doesn't matter.
They were late, anyway.
Besides, they never told me, so...
If you get something, you give back!
Even elementary school kids know that.
Do you think I should get them something?
Uesugi.
I was texting with Itsuki yesterday.
We decided to come shopping together.
Anyway, their birthday...
Shh! Shh!
So you are here with her.
In that case, we can't shop together.
I might know what to get them
if I watch how they shop.
Wh-Why are you following me?
We're shopping for the same trip anyway.
What's the problem?
Yes, we are.
But while they may share a purpose,
they're totally different things.
I'm here to buy underwear!
R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-Raiha,
what do you think of this?
I think that's way too adult, I-Itsuki.
I'm a h-h-h-h-high schooler, after all.
This is about right.
Don't you need to shop?
I tend to take good care of my things.
You're still wearing little girl panties?
H-How did you know?!
Thanks for waiting.
Huh?
Where's Itsuki?
She's taking her own measurements
and trying some clothes on.
You're quintuplets.
Couldn't she just buy the same sizes?
That's quintuplet harassment.
Quintassment!
I don't know why she's taking
measurements, though.
She hasn't grown more
than the rest of us, has she?
I guess things are complicated
for quintuplets, huh?
They are!
Especially these days!
N-No, anyway, school camp
ended pretty badly,
so let's make sure we don't regret
anything on our school trip.
Not that I really care, but I'll
be sure to take care of my health.
Sheesh. You act like you aren't
looking forward to it.
He's been looking through the guidebook
over and over at home.
Raiha!
Besides, you might run into
the girl from the photo.
That won't happen.
Huh? Wasn't that in Kyoto?
That's what Dad said.
Even then, she was a tourist, too.
What girl in the photo?
Come on, you should show her.
It's nothing.
I don't even have the photo anymore.
Something smells fishy.
You should be able to tell me,
if it's actually nothing.
I know why you can't tell me!
It's because you have regrets!
Now, tell me, and get it off your chest!
She's a girl I ran into in Kyoto.
Her name is Rena.
Rena...
The end.
The end?!
B-But you've got me curious!
I want to hear a little more! Please!
She's basically his first love.
F-First love?!
Hey! No one ever said...
Full house.
I lost.
One more time!
We're playing one more game!
I'll take you on anytime.
Miku.
Miku, the game's done.
Two pair.
So slow! And weak!
You seem sleepy.
I noticed you woke up early
and went somewhere.
Yeah.
I begged my workplace to
let me borrow the kitchen.
So are you going to have him try it, and...
You've worked so hard for this day.
I'm rooting for you until the end.
I hope it's still good when it's cold.
I know.
How about the next person who wins
gets to ask anyone else to do anything?
Anything, huh?
Sounds good.
Challenge accepted.
I'll win.
These sparks...
We're just really into this card game, right?
We'll have your large luggage
taken to the hotel.
Bring only your valuables.
That's it for instructions.
Dismissed.
Is something wrong?
No, I think I just imagined it.
I wonder where Fu's group is going.
Is there anywhere you all want to go?
Well, if you're going to travel,
you have to go shopping.
Fancy shops are way more fun
than some old temples.
You don't get it.
We're in Kyoto, of all places.
You want him to try
some of the local delicacies.
I agree with that too, but...
At the moment, I'd like to remind him of
what happened that day here at this station.
I mean, we could go explore.
Itsuki, what's gotten into you?
I...
Futaro's group left.
The only reason we wouldn't agree
to meet up with them
is because we're all thinking the same thing.
We're following them.
Do these go on forever?
I've seen pictures of them,
but they're stunning in person.
This is so grammable.
Come on, everyone, peace signs.
It's kind of rare that we get a
picture of just us sisters, huh?
Oh, don't we have any of just the five of us?
Didn't we take one
at the fireworks festival?
We haven't taken one since we were
on our field trip back in elementary school.
Let's get a picture of
all of us this time, then.
Do you think Futaro's at the top already?
I haven't gotten a glimpse of him.
Guys are fast.
All right, we need to keep up!
This stairway's... pretty long... huh?
My legs are starting to hurt.
Come on, everyone! You're so slow!
She doesn't have a care in the world.
That's what we love about her.
You're right.
She's nothing like a certain
schemer that I know.
You're coming up with some
nasty plan again, aren't you?
Me? I would never!
There are two ways we can go.
It looks like both lead to the peak.
Which way has Fu gone?
I'll fall behind pretty badly
if I don't meet him here.
It's already noon.
Let's have lunch at that shop over there.
Wait, lunch...
What?
Is there something else you want?
U-Um...
Full house!
I win!
Let's split into two groups.
Miku and I will take the right route.
Ichika, Nino, and Itsuki
will take the left route.
That way, we'll run into
Uesugi at some point.
Hang on a second.
You can't decide that for us.
I am the victor! My orders are absolute!
I have the right to order you to do anything!
Look what happened because
of your stupid idea.
Judging from the flow of people,
the other route was the right one.
Um...
What are you two talking about?
It's a washroom.
I wanted to go.
I guess we took the right route.
There aren't any ahead, are there?
I guess I should go, too.
Miku!
Hurry up, or lunchtime's going to be over!
Just a little longer.
You worked so hard for this day.
Hang in there just a little longer.
Yotsuba...
Thanks.
It's lunchtime.
I'm getting hungry.
I wonder what Fu's group
had planned for lunch?
Huh?
Where's Ichika?
Shoot!
From what I saw on the map,
this is the shorter route to the peak.
I might not be able to beat
Yotsuba when she's by herself,
but given Miku's fitness,
I should be able to beat them to the peak.
What do I do when I meet Futaro?
Those other guys will be there, too.
Still, Miku's been suspicious.
She's going to make a move
sometime during this school trip.
I have to do it again.
If I can't take back the lie
I've already told,
all I can do is continue to lie
in order to stop Miku.
No one's here.
We didn't run into each other along the way,
which must mean Futaro
took the right route.
I have to hurry.
I ran a lot. Miku and Yotsuba
can't be here yet.
Ichika.
Why are you dressed up as me?
If there's a reason for this...
Ichika, this wasn't what I meant.
Is this what you really wanted to do?
Yotsuba, what do you mean?
Ichika's trying to get in the way.
Get in the way of what?
In the way of...
Yotsuba, wait!
your confession to Uesugi, Miku!
Okay... I made it first.
Huh?
What did you just say?
Uesugi, did you just hear that?
Miku!
We're finally at the peak.
Wait, please!
Where are you going?
Ichika, you crossed the line.
I'm getting fed up with you.
Are you happy about making her cry?
Wait, Nino, that was my...
Yotsuba, it's fine.
No matter the result... this is
more or less what I was trying to do.
How low are you going to...
I don't want to hear that from you.
You said at the hot springs that you
would walk over anyone to make it work.
How are we any different?
Tell me.
I did say that.
I don't intend on giving
him up to anyone else.
But the bond between the five of us
is just as important to me.
Even if you were the one
who was chosen someday,
I would have wanted to celebrate.
I can't walk another step.
Honestly,
you ate too much at the restaurant below.
Huh?
What are you doing?
I mean, I don't know what's going on, either.
Girls, take it down a notch.
Shut up and stay out of this!
You'll make things even messier!
Go chase after Miku!
What?
Hurry up!
On the double!
Fine.
Sorry, guys.
I'll meet you up ahead.
Right.
I-I'll go find her, too.
We're going down, too.
Okay.
Shit, Miku's not here anymore.
I got through to Itsuki!
She's on the bus with Miku.
Okay.
Let's take the bus.
Uesugi, you heard what
I said at the peak, right?
I didn't hear nothing.
Ah! You definitely heard!
I said I didn't hear anything.
Just leave it at that!
Still, it's a fact that my
reckless comment hurt Miku.
She's been working so hard.
And I'm the one who gave Ichika the idea
to do this, too... during our family trip...
You're right. It's your fault.
Consider the time and place
before saying something like that.
So you did hear me.
I mean, I knew, I guess.
You knew? You knew what?
I mean, you know, that...
M-
that Miku has had feelings for me.
Am I hearing things?
Could you say that again?
Stop it! I'm not saying it again!
Uesugi the Dense...
I can't believe it.
Well, a lot's happened.
So I was really confused when she,
of all people, said she was cheering "us" on.
That wasn't really Miku.
I was right about that, huh?
I said, it's fine.
You worry about people too much.
To be honest, you take it way too far.
I'm okay with that.
Remember I told you before about how
when I failed, everyone came with me?
I dragged them all into my problems.
It's not something I can make up for so easily.
It's only natural that they
should end up happier than I do.
Is that how it has to be?
I wanted everyone to enjoy this trip, too.
Is there any way everyone
can be happy, Uesugi?
There is.
If each person could feel happy without
comparing themselves to others...
That would be the kind of
world that you're looking for.
Then...
But...
In reality, it's not uncommon for someone's
happiness to make someone else unhappy.
Some kinds of happiness are gained only
by competing and taking from each other.
In that case, what can I do?
There's nothing you can do.
There's a limit.
Don't you think it's a little presumptuous?
Trying to get everything.
When you choose to have something,
you choose not to have something else.
Someday, you'll have to choose.
Someday, for sure.
Listen up, everyone.
We're being tailed by a sneak photographer.
I noticed it ever since
we were at Kyoto Station.
I'm sure of it.
I read in the news that they
target students on school trips.
Even then, why would they target you, Nino?
What is that supposed to mean?!
I knew it!
It's a feast!
Let's post it on Instagram.
Anyway, Miku and Ichika are
back at the hotel, right?
Yes.
Both of them seem worn out
after all that walking.
They're resting in our room.
I doubt they're in the same room together.
I can't believe Miku set out on her own.
I'm going to go check on them.
Hold it.
I'm almost done eating.
I'll come with you.
Nino!
Hey, Uesugi, is something the matter?
What happened to Maeda?
A long bathroom visit.
Me too, then.
Which means I'm coming, too.
Don't follow me.
Miku, Ichika, I know you're in there.
Open the door.
They aren't responding.
They're ignoring their phones, too.
Miku, I'm sorry.
I ruined everything!
But there are still two more
days on the school trip.
I want you to let me make things right.
Yotsuba didn't do anything wrong.
Yotsuba...
After what you said, Nino,
now I'm hearing things, too!
Y-Yeah, right?
We're just hearing things.
There's no way he'd be in the hotel.
What was that scream?
What's—
Nino, what was that scream?
You finally picked up.
Ichika.
You...
Futaro, I'm glad I ran into you.
Do you have time tomorrow?
Miku, do you have any plans for tomorrow?
There's something I want
to talk to you about.
You can see all the way to the station.
What if we fall?
It feels higher, seeing it for
the first time in a while.
Uesugi.
I thought you were with your friends.
Oh, I wanted to talk to Miku.
I thought she'd be with you.
Miku isn't here.
She doesn't seem to be well yet.
She's resting at the hotel.
And Ichika and Nino are walking around
with their friends from second year.
I'm worried about Miku, but...
Yeah, so the two of us
are spending our time together.
It's kind of sad seeing less than half of you.
I-It's not bad, for a change.
Hey, we're at Kiyomizu Temple!
Itsuki?
Look at this scenery, Uesugi!
It's gorgeous!
Quit tugging!
It's dangerous!
You're afraid of this?
And you call yourself a man?
I-I'm not scared at all.
You must be freaking out yourself.
Oh, I know.
Let's take a picture together.
Here.
Huh?
Why?!
Please, Yotsuba.
Sure, I guess.
Hurry up and get it over with.
O-Okay.
Thank you for taking the time.
Why am I being so bold?
But this ought to be enough to make him
remember what happened six years ago.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I'm sorry you have to spend
your school trip like this.
I'm going to rest in my room
for a while longer.
Sure... Oh, right.
There's been a sneak photographer
spotted in this hotel.
Be careful.
Thank you.
"Like the shadows, unknowable," was it?
What are you doing, Nino?
Imitating you.
In more ways than one.
They wouldn't buy that two sisters
are both staying in sick together.
When's the next head count?
Yeah, we have some time.
I'm asking why you came here.
I told you.
I wanted to talk to you.
If you came to cheer me up, forget it.
Huh?
Why would I do such a thing?
My rival just backed down by herself.
It's nothing but lucky for me.
All I need to do now is defeat Ichika.
That sly fox...
What should I do with her?
Anyway, I'm taking Fu.
You okay with that?
"Fu"...
Since when have you...
What?
Are you going to tell me you aren't going
to give him up because you liked him first?
I don't mean that.
Sure, you might have been first.
I don't really know enough to
say time doesn't matter in love.
This is my first time.
I have no idea what's right or wrong.
All I know is that I love him
more than anyone.
I haven't given up, either.
The school trip is a perfect
chance to get close to him,
and you're spending it locked in this room.
You've practically given up.
Your turn's over.
Bye, loser.
I don't want to give up!
But I'm scared.
I knew it would end up like this.
But now that Futaro knows how I feel,
I don't know if I'm good enough for him.
There's no way he would like someone like me.
I never thought it would be
so scary to fight fair and square.
Look, Itsuki.
Good luck charms for love.
Let's buy one for Miku.
Um... Where's Uesugi?
He must have gone back to his friends.
This was supposed to be my chance.
Itsuki.
Are you hiding something from me?
You have to tell Uesugi.
That you were the one who
met him six years ago.
"Sisters War: Part 2."