We're going to be third-years
starting next week.
We're the most senior people at school.
I'm so glad we didn't fail.
Let's keep up the pace, everyone.
Yup.
Oh, and from next week,
we're going to split the rent five ways.
If you can't pay, you'll be
sent back to our old apartment.
Let's all work hard so we can stay together.
There you have it!
Ball's in your court now.
So...
I'm glad you saw the ad and decided
to come in for an interview.
Why are you trying to work here?!
I want to know why she's here, too.
I'd love to hire both of you,
but we only need one.
If Uesugi were to quit...
Oh, come on, Boss...
I'd like to make cakes.
You're good at it, huh?
Then you can...
H-Hey!
I'm better than her!
I've made chocolates tons of times this year.
Seriously? That was with my help!
I managed to make it on my own in the end.
These girls are your friends, aren't they?
Huh? I guess.
You deal with it.
What?!
Futaro, what are you going to do?
You'd obviously choose me, right?
I'll do anything you need.
So choose me.
Okay, I look forward to working
with you starting next week.
I lost.
You shouldn't have asked for a cook-off.
Did you seriously think you could win?
I do feel bad, though.
The bakery across the street is hiring, too.
I think I'll work there.
You moved on surprisingly quickly.
Are you sure? You won't get
to work with him there.
Yeah.
Futaro isn't my objective.
I realized when I made that cake today...
It doesn't taste bad, though, really...
I like making things.
Besides...
I'm going to become a version of me
that Futaro would fall in love with.
I don't feel like I've won.
But I'm going to make him
fall for me at this job.
Oh, yeah?
I wonder if I've caused them
trouble with what I said.
Do you not make enough on your own to get by?
We can make it work, just barely.
But I've been focusing on surefire gigs
so that I can make rent.
And I want to move on to stuff
that'll really challenge and motivate me.
I see.
I heard Yotsuba got hired, too.
She'd been cleaning my room,
so she's already an expert.
Itsuki's still struggling to make
her first move, but she'll be fine.
I don't care what you do,
as long as you don't fail.
I wouldn't want to fail
after we've come so far.
I'm counting on you, Teacher.
Is something wrong?
No.
You know, though...
I know it was my idea,
but it makes me a little sad.
Everyone's going to be busy.
We won't have as many
opportunities to be together.
I wonder if this is how we're going
to grow up and drift apart.
Dunno.
But I'm sure it's not a bad thing.
You're right.
Long story short, this concern
would prove to be short-lived.
The bond between these five turned out
to be far stronger than I'd imagined.
They're quintuplets!
Insane.
It's enough that you look the same.
I knew the Nakanos were quintuplets...
But seeing them together in
person is pretty amazing.
Can I call you by your first name,
so it's not so confusing?
Sure, we'd appreciate that, too.
Do that trick where you guess
the same card together.
Sorry, we don't have telepathy or anything.
You look like them, too,
don't you, Miku?
Show me your face more!
Please, everyone, calm down.
Move.
What?
Are you curious about them, too, Uesugi?
Bathroom.
You're in my way. Move.
What's wrong with him?
What an ass.
He walked right past us.
Business as usual.
Uesugi's been like
that since second year.
He seems to be deliberately trying not
to involve himself with his classmates.
Oh, yeah, he tried to do his duties
at school camp on his own.
That's just how he is.
I wish people could know that
he's a good person at heart.
You're all third-years starting today.
As seniors, you need to behave in a way
that inspires your underclassmen to—
Yes?
I'm announcing my bid for the
position of class representative.
What?
No one asked yet.
I'm begging!
Please let me do it!
I never said no, either.
I mean, if no one else wants to...
If you all ever need anything,
just let me know.
Why don't we choose our male
representative, too, then?
Does anyone want to run?
Anyone?
You can nominate someone, too.
Go ahead.
Yotsuba's so embarrassing.
It's obvious who's going
to be the male class rep.
It's definitely going to be Takeda.
He had the highest grade on the finals, too.
Sheesh, you guys.
Teacher, I know someone perfectly
suited for the role.
Oh?
Uesugi Futaro!
Huh?!
Is Uesugi really cut out for it?
She's not going to even consider Takeda?
Yotsuba... What have you done?!
All right, shall we move on to our next role?
Teacher, I never said I'd do it.
Damn that Yotsuba! Who asked her?!
Futaro, do you have a minute?
I want to ask you something.
There's a magic lamp here.
There isn't.
There is.
Is this a psychological test?
If it could grant you five wishes,
what would they be?
Where's this coming from?
This is a psychological test, isn't it?
Would anyone answer anything
other than to become rich?
Money...
Will that do?
Four more.
Why isn't it three in total?!
You can ask for anything.
You can use magic, you know?
I've thought about wanting more stamina,
but working more would only wear me out more,
so faster recovery times would be nice.
I don't sleep well these days, either.
And I could do with some better luck, too.
Got it.
What did you get?
Huh?
Why won't you tell me?
There you are!
Yotsuba!
Teacher was calling you.
Come on!
Uh...
That's not Yotsuba.
That's Miku, the middle sister.
Really?
Sorry. We're still learning who's who.
It's okay, I'm used to it.
Hey, Yotsuba, Teacher's calling.
They get it wrong without fail!
Listen, to make it easy, just remember
who they are by their accessories.
This utterly tacky hairpin
is the fifth sister, Itsuki.
That was completely uncalled for.
Yotsuba is the one with
the gaudy ribbon.
Keep that in mind, and you'll be fine.
Not that I'm in any position
to lecture them...
Wow, Uesugi.
Thanks.
No wonder you're the class rep.
Teach us more about the five!
Look, there's another one over there.
Hey!
Yotsuba!
No, that one is Nino!
Those girls...
They're being too clingy with Futaro...
It's not a bad thing.
I think he's changing, too.
I understand getting a
little jealous, though.
A-As a friend, I mean.
It still makes no sense to me, though.
How could anyone fall in love with him?
I asked Futaro what his five wishes would be.
None of these work.
What should we do?
In any case, we should hurry.
Yeah, it's coming up.
Futaro's birthday's almost here.
Class Rep Uesugi!
I want to talk to Miku.
Class Rep!
Could you hand this to Ichika?
For Nino.
For Itsuki.
For Yotsuba.
This is such a pain!
Uh, now that we are third-years...
Pardon me.
Class Rep Uesugi, you're talking
too quietly. I can't hear you.
Could you be a little louder?
I'd like to discuss what's arguably
the biggest event of the first term.
It begins!
The national mock exams!
The school trip!
Let's all have fun!
Whoo!
Really? That?
Nino, are you going to work?
Yes.
Today's the first day.
Can I ask you for a favor, then?
What do you want now?
I'm not switching with you.
If you're going to be with Futaro,
could you find some information for his gift?
Huh? Me?
You're sure?
Yeah.
I have to go to work starting today, too.
I have to work hard to make
him happy on his birthday.
You've got some confidence,
letting me make the move.
A lot happened during spring break,
but I'm in the lead...
I think.
So why am I feeling so anxious?
I don't think it worked out that way for me.
I confessed to him.
There's no way it hasn't had
an effect on him, right?
Oh, are you starting today?
Y-Yeah, I am.
They're letting me into the kitchen already.
By the way, what do you think of my hair?
Well, it looks like it's suited for work.
Don't drag me down.
Who do you think I am?
This job is a piece of cake.
You may be in charge of the chores,
but you're still a spoiled rich girl.
You're about to learn how hard
work—the real world—truly is!
Amazing! It's perfect!
I can't believe you pulled
this off on your first day.
You're a genius.
Am I?
You're just good at teaching, Boss.
If anything, I feel like he's
more distant than before.
Maybe I shouldn't have confessed.
Man, I'm so glad you joined us, Nakano.
We have an important reservation tonight.
Oh, yeah, all the part-timers
are working today.
Is a large group coming in?
No, just one person.
A famous reviewer,
known to those in the know.
May.
Her evaluations are said
to be so accurate that
a shop's customers are multiplied by the
number of stars she gives it on review sites.
And she wants to try our new spring dish.
For five stars!
Yes!
I need to work hard.
I have to become part of the team here
and get closer to Futaro soon.
Boss, this batter...
It doesn't taste quite right.
Indeed...
I'm sorry! That one's mine.
Let's redo it.
O-Okay.
I'm going for a break.
Okay.
Nakano, take a break while you can, too.
No, I can keep going.
I want to keep going.
You should take breaks
when you have the chance to.
This must have been especially
hard for you as a newcomer.
Sorry.
Okay.
I understand.
What do I do?
Everyone seemed busy because of me.
I should go back and...
The boss said it, too.
It's not your fault.
It's entirely the boss's fault for
pushing the work onto a new recruit.
But it's not usually a problem.
Why did it have to happen today?
I embarrassed myself in front of Futaro.
Take a look at this.
But don't get too good of a look.
They're Santa decorations that I accidentally
bought a thousand of instead of a hundred.
Huh?
Also, the dent on this rack...
This is from when I fell.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I can't count the number of times I served
cakes to the wrong customers or broke dishes.
Compared to that, your mistake was trivial.
Are you trying to cheer me up?
N-No, I'm not!
I'm trying to teach you how brutal work is!
I'm your senior, technically.
Why?
Why are you avoiding me, then?
Sorry to make things awkward for you.
It must be hard working with me.
I've worked a ton of jobs, but every
time something happens, I realize
all I'm ever good for is studying.
All I am is smart, the top of the class,
and easily qualified to tutor the five of you.
You sound way too confident.
So this is the first time...
that anyone's told me they loved me.
I didn't know how to talk to you.
But I'll answer now.
How I feel about you is—
Wait!
I know you don't like me.
I've been so nasty to you.
But don't make up your mind yet.
We're finally working together, and I
haven't gotten to tell you anything yet.
So I want you to know me better.
I want you to really know
how much I love you!
That so?
Perfect timing, you two.
Miss May has arrived.
Got it. I'll be right there.
What's wrong, Uesugi?
Your face is red up to your ears.
No, this is...
Best be ready,
Fu.
That's Miss May.
I'll go take her order.
We're in the middle of work!
What the hell are you doing, Itsuki?
It can't be...
How did you know?!
Morning.
Ichika.
It's almost fishy how often I
bump into you on the way to school.
Huh? Oh...
Aren't the other girls with you?
I came to buy this. It's just
a coincidence that I ran into you.
Oh, this is for you.
You got it for me when you
didn't know you'd run into me?
I can't drink coffee, though.
It's too bitter.
I-I'll have it, then.
Yum.
Let's go, before we're late.
I blew it.
The offering plan didn't work.
I could never go for a direct
attack like Nino, though.
But I don't ever want to
give up this position.
Did you always wear glasses?
You never noticed?
You sure are dense.
Well?
Do I look a little smarter?
It's supposed to be a disguise, actually.
A disguise?
There was a screening yesterday
for the movie I was in.
It got a decent amount of
attention on TV and stuff.
Remember? It's that movie from way back.
You were disguising yourself
so people won't talk to you?
How very Hollywood!
Hey!
You're embarrassing me! Stop it!
You're all masters of disguise, aren't you?
Oh, I like that.
We keep all this on us for
these kinds of occasions.
I could probably pull off
Yotsuba or Miku right away.
Oh, I could do Nino.
Maybe I shouldn't. You wouldn't
be able to tell me apart.
I wish you wouldn't underestimate me.
Just the other day, I managed to see
through Miku's disguise without any hints.
Is that...
Huh?
Aren't they your sisters?
I'll show you just how wrong you are.
Come on, Itsuki. She's eating again.
Yotsuba's so loud.
Don't.
I was shocked when Nino
came to work at my shop,
but I was even more shocked hearing Miku
is working at the bakery across the street.
Please, stop.
My boss was happy that our rival
business had suddenly lost business.
Please don't talk about the other girls.
Wait.
Nobody else.
I want you to keep your eyes on me alone.
Hey...
Let's skip class together.
No way.
Why not?! Just a little!
That's crazy!
We're going to be late
thanks to your whining!
Jeez, you're so proper, Futaro.
You already skip tutoring
sessions enough as it is.
Get your act together!
Skip?
I've been working, you know.
We barely made it.
Things just aren't working out.
I saw the news this morning, Ichika!
Are you actually an actress?!
I'm so surprised.
I never knew we had a star in our class.
Was it such a big movie?
Y-Yeah.
Not that I care.
Good on you for clearing that audition.
You're a good liar now.
Is it bad that I'm so simple?
You paid attention to me and remembered...
That fact alone touches me more
than any of our classmates' praise.
Hey, Ichika.
I'll see you at the library.
I'm coming.
But I want to talk to you more.
Just a little longer.
Sorry, I have a study group.
Huh? Where did Ichika go?
Sorry.
You're still here?
Let's go, Miku.
Sorry, it's me...
It's already releasing, huh?
Time flies.
Huh? What?
Ichika's movie.
You were the one
who told me about it yesterday.
I see.
Miku did.
A lot's happened since then.
Not just with me, but probably
with the others, too.
I guess I was never going to be special.
Do as you wish.
I'm going to win.
I'd walk over them to get with him.
I don't want you to hold back.
I want you to do what
you want to do.
Futaro—
Futaro.
Yes?
Futaro, can I tell you something?
Ichika likes you.
I think you'd look good together.
I'm rooting for you two.
You're not serious, right?
Oh, I'm very serious.
"Five Cranes in Return!"