You were late today, Ebata.
I apologize.
It's fine. But I must ask...
Why are you dressed that way?
Whatever makes you happy.
Yes, all five are working hard.
I see.
Then I expect good things from their finals.
May I say something?
I have a bit of a selfish request.
What is it?
I'd like to quit tutoring as of today.
Are you aware that Nino and Itsuki
got in a fight and ran away from home?
I never heard about this.
Have they resolved their issues?
Yes.
Great.
Goodbye.
Is that it?
Aren't you curious about
why they got in a fight?
Don't you care to know what they're thinking or what's bothering them?
Oh, sorry, I shouldn't talk like that to my employer.
Oh, wait, I'm quitting.
Why don't you try acting
like a father like once?!
Asshole!
Uesugi... You've gone and done it now.
But...
I won't give my daughters to a man like you.
Thank you, Grandpa!
I'd always gotten allowances until last year.
I should have stayed home to study.
"Good fortune"!
Yay!
What about you?
I don't need my fortune told
to know how my year's going to be.
Ever since I met those girls,
I've always had...
the worst luck.
Uesugi and Raiha!
Why are you always around?
Why don't you stop by our place?
Nah, we'll pass.
I'll go!
I love you, too.
They kissed...
It's so romantic.
Why did you even invite us over?
Come on, it's the new year. Let's relax.
Happy New Year, Futaro.
I made a New Year's meal.
Want some?
Huh?
What's wrong, Raiha?
Um...
I think I had the wrong idea about you all.
I'd heard your family was really rich.
O-Oh, well, things happened.
Sorry we don't really have much.
We have to return the kimonos
to our landlord, too.
Anyway, you can make yourself at home.
Okay.
Are you guys sure you're all right?
Hey.
Why are you sitting over there?
Isn't it cold?
Get in the kotatsu.
Okay, Raiha, go.
Come on, don't be shy.
I'll give you a massage.
You must be tired.
No, I'm not really tired.
No fair, Ichika.
First come, first served.
I get his arms, then!
Oh, fine.
I'd like to massage his legs, then.
Brother's popular all of a sudden!
Mom, spring has come early for Big Brother.
What are you guys plotting?
Urp.
I-It's nothing.
We're just thanking you for everything.
Liar!
You always work so hard.
Something's really fishy.
Please have some of my food, if you'd like.
Way too fishy.
Let's play the face matching game
to get into the party mood.
We made a quintuplets version!
That's way too hard!
Um...
There's something we'd like to discuss with you.
It's too early for that!
Why don't we all go to the other room?
What are they scheming?
What should we do?
I don't think it bothers him at all.
I'd feel bad, though.
We're asking him to continue
teaching us without pay.
I want to do something for him.
And I don't want to depend on Father,
if we can avoid it.
But what is there that we could do for him?
Th-That's inappropriate!
You were thinking the same thing,
weren't you?
I can't imagine that'd make Futaro happy.
Who knows? He's a guy, after all.
You're an actress, aren't you?
You could give him a peck on the cheek.
Wh-What exactly do you think actresses do?
B-But I mean, in that case...
What about you, Miku?
Me?
And Futaro...
Futaro.
Smooch.
Miku!
You've really led me on.
You can't stop me now.
N-No, Futaro.
Stop.
Wait, don't stop.
You stop!
Uh...
What are you all talking about?
Why not just do something
normal and cook for him?
You're good at cooking, Nino.
Make him some snacks or something.
I can't.
I was finally getting over it.
Why don't we just go tell him
what's going on?
Ichika.
Don't move.
Wh-What?
No!
I knew it!
This is Ichika's mouth.
No doubt.
I'm pretty sure it's this one.
You guys are playing!
We changed the rules, though.
Yotsuba, what about this?
Let's see...
Uesugi, you have cream on your face.
B-Brother! Yotsuba!
Let's just call that peck on the cheek
a payment for your tutoring.
I didn't expect that from Yotsuba.
She caught me off-guard.
I'm dead!
Payment?
About that...
We aren't in any position to
compensate you fairly right now.
Oh, you could have said so.
I'm just doing it because I want to.
Don't worry about paying me.
Uesugi.
You can just give me a cut
when you make it big.
But I want it in writing! Five thousand yen
per person per day of tutoring!
And I will collect, right down to the last yen!
Right, that's how he is.
And all five of you are here right now.
Let's get cracking on the winter homework!
Winter homework, huh?
Futaro.
You underestimate us.
We've all done our homework already.
Oh.
Well, let's just make it a
regular study session, then.
Big Brother.
I'm going to go home
so I don't get in the way.
O-Okay.
Stay safe.
Futaro.
Can you help me with this bit?
Let's see.
"Provide examples of words ending with -ish"?
-ish is a suffix that means "approximately,"
or kind of. So you have "pinkish"...
"Bookish," "thickish"...
There's also peckish, but that's...
What?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Hey, Ichika, wake up.
Sorry.
I'm not... sleeping.
Yeah, you are!
Hey.
Let her sleep for a while.
Ichika's been working even more than before.
She is paying our bills and expenses.
It's all thanks to Ichika
that we get to have you here to teach us.
But what's the point
if she can't focus on studying?
Hey, wake...
Guys...
Why don't we work, too?
Do you have any work experience?
I-I do not.
Will you have time to both study and work?
All of you are struggling to even pass.
I'll work as a tutor, like you do.
I'll teach as I study.
That way, I can improve
my academics, too.
It's two birds with one stone.
Please don't.
I'd feel sorry for your students.
How about working at a supermarket, then?
You'd be fired instantly.
I want to try working at a maid café.
You might be surprisingly popular.
Permission denied!
You'd probably be
a dominatrix, right, Nino?
What's that supposed to mean?
Nino would work in food service, right?
If I had to choose, sure.
It's always been your dream
to open your own shop.
First I've heard of it.
It's just a silly idea I had as a kid.
Don't take it too seriously.
I know a good cake shop.
Mille-feuille.
Eclairs.
Mont Blanc.
Merci beaucoup.
No!
I've worked several jobs so far,
but they all took some commitment.
Don't underestimate work!
Now's the time to study!
Futaro!
Ichika! Please stop
taking your clothes off in your sleep!
Look away! Pervert!
Me?!
I underestimated this job.
Hello?
It's been a while, Itsuki.
Father.
Well? What do you think of my pie?
It's just like yours, boss!
Give me a raise, please!
Give it a taste.
It's underdone.
I shouldn't be talking trash about Miku.
Looks like it'll be a while
before I can let you in the kitchen.
Oh, that reminds me...
Uesugi, you can leave now.
No...
Are you firing me?
We're closing at noon today.
We're renting the shop out
for a movie shoot.
You could have told me sooner.
Hello!
Looking forward to working with you today.
If the movie takes off,
the fans will be coming in
droves to visit the site.
We'll have a pick with our business name
in the cakes that will be on the screen.
I wish I had his insatiable hunger.
That looks so good.
I look forward to working with you.
H-Hi.
I should go home.
Thank you for having us.
Scene 37-4.
Action!
I've always wanted to try this cake shop.
Now's not the time, Tamako!
Huh? What do you mean?
That's the cursed reply.
They say if you get one, you die.
I'm too dumb to know
what you're talking about.
Let's just have some cake!
What, Tamako?
Futaro,
would you mind not watching?
It's embarrassing.
Why would you take up embarrassing work?
I'm trying not to tell the others,
but we're running out of savings.
I mean, it turns out food and power
is a lot more expensive than I thought.
So I decided to accept any work I can find.
I have to be strong for the girls.
So don't try to stop me.
I'm not going to dismiss your efforts.
And I'm grateful to you for giving me
an opportunity to continue tutoring.
But I'm sure you could do better.
Isn't this job still pretty unprofitable
for how much it ties you down?
Miss Nakano, we're ready to start rolling.
Coming.
Yummy!
Cut!
That was good.
That one was good,
but why don't we try another take?
Okay.
I wish the others could see her
being so ditzy.
I hope you don't mind us using
this pie for one more take.
Sure.
The pick's missing.
It's the dud that I made!
Ready! Action!
Yummy!
Nice! That was great!
You got Problem 5 wrong.
You caught me.
You don't have anything to hide.
These things are only cool
when done in secret.
Are you done with your script?
Yeah.
I memorized the whole thing already.
Why can't you use that skill for studying?
The curse kills me in the first part,
so I don't have that many lines.
You die a lot, huh?
Oh, yeah.
Is the cake here all right?
If I'm being kind, it was unique.
If I'm being brutal,
it was like Miku's home cooking.
Sorry about that.
But you saved my skin.
That was an impressive lie.
You surprise me.
It's called acting.
It's true that you surprised me, though.
I mean, well...
Y-You're kind of growing into
your job as an actress.
She's asleep!
Jeez.
She almost had me saying
something smug to her.
Man, I'm amazed you can hide your
embarrassment in front of so many people.
I really wish the others could see you.
Good work, Ichika.
I hate that I'm even acting
in this moment...
Now I really am lying.
But I couldn't let him see my face right now.
So heavy!
Stay calm...
Remember your mechanics!
The most efficient way of carrying this load is...
I can't!
I'll carry it.
Hurry up, you bag handlers.
Jeez.
Why'd you call me out at this hour?
They're having a sale today.
And you should be able
to carry that yourself.
You carry it, then.
Oh, right...
Miku asked me to buy these.
She's eating all that?
You're pretty dense for
someone who's so smart.
It's so early, too. It's only January.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, Nino.
Can you hold this for a sec?
Hey—
I told you!
Hold on tight.
There.
Sorry, Nino.
Y-Yeah.
Something's weird lately.
Maybe I haven't gotten over Kintaro yet.
It doesn't make sense otherwise.
Yeah.
There's no way...
There's no way this guy's my prince!
What?
Nothing.
Nino, look.
Excuse me.
Bring us every kind of sandwich you have.
Certainly.
Don't worry about me.
You don't want anything?
I'll take them. Thank you.
Good girl.
You're amenable and quick
to understand, Itsuki.
I believe that's what is meant
when one is called "intelligent."
I knew it. It's Dad.
Why is he with Itsuki?
That was definitely him.
That was him at the hospital back then.
That man is their father?
Now, Itsuki...
I'll turn a blind eye to the mistake
you girls have made.
Come back home with the others immediately.
Inform all of your sisters.
Does that include him as well?
You mean Uesugi?
This is a family matter.
He's an outsider in every sense.
And, to be honest,
I hate him.
That's so childish!
What did you do to Dad?
I-I dunno.
G-Gee, I'm not sure.
We can't go home yet.
He's far too involved in this
to call him an outsider.
Then how about this:
I'll allow Uesugi back into the home,
and ask him to continue tutoring.
But he'll be working alongside
a professional tutor.
He'll be acting as her support.
But we're all working so hard.
Do you even suppose, if Uesugi was
brought back in as your tutor as before,
that Yotsuba could earn a passing grade?
From what I've seen of her grades in
the second term, I have very little hope.
No.
You'll only make things worse if you go.
But...
Y-You're right.
We'll have a better chance with two tutors.
We can do it.
Yotsuba!
Uesugi and the five of us can do it.
I want the six of us to pull it off.
So please, believe in us.
We won't make the same mistake again.
And if you do?
I would rather not say this out loud,
but I've made an arrangement
with an acquaintance
who is a board member at a high school that
would allow you to enroll as third-years.
If you fail on the next exam,
I'll have you transfer to that school.
If you insist on doing things your way,
the responsibility is all yours.
I hope you understand.
Understood.
I knew you would, Itsuki.
Then I'll finalize the arrangements.
No.
We'll accept the condition that we
transfer schools if we don't make it.
I'm sorry I'm not an amenable,
understanding, intelligent child.
It seems that the duty of a parent is to
hear the selfish demands of their children.
And it's also the duty of a parent
to scold their selfishness.
This is your last chance.
"The Last Exam."