This is your last chance.
He's gone.
Uesugi! Did you see all that?
He's as scary a dad as I imagined.
Yeah.
He's absolutely in the right.
But some things matter more than being right.
I never thought he'd bring up transferring.
Now I really can't afford to fail.
I'm sorry for getting you caught up
in our family matters.
I don't want to transfer.
But that's not my concern.
Whether it's your circumstances,
or your family's circumstances,
or your previous school,
or this transfer ultimatum...
None of it matters.
I'm going to do as I please.
And I'm going to make you all pass!
I'm going to make you all graduate
with your heads held high.
That's all I'm thinking about!
That's encouraging.
I have my promise with Father,
but unless I can pass this exam
and move on to the next grade,
my dreams won't matter.
Passing isn't my only goal on this exam.
I decided back on that day that
I would beat my sisters.
Don't think about anything else.
I need to focus on passing.
This can't be...
This can't be happening.
Me? With him, of all people?
I've kept messing up until now.
But please, gods of studying,
give me your strength this time.
We all worked so hard together!
We have two months until final exams.
Let's get started with our lessons, everyone!
Please do begin!
And find out for us what we
need to do to pass the exams!
Y-Yeah.
I'm glad you're enthusiastic.
Anyway, let's start.
Our goal is to get over 30 percent!
What's the matter?
Maybe he's been reading something dirty.
It's her fault.
She's been force feeding me
chocolates lately for some reason.
I brought some again.
Hey, I've been craving something sweet.
I'm not giving you any.
What? Quit being so greedy.
I'm not.
Not yet.
Have all of these and tell me what you think.
What kind of punishment is this?
You're still up?
Ichika.
Did I wake you? Sorry.
You must have a good idea of
Futaro's tastes by now.
So you realized.
I don't like sweet stuff,
so I don't know what to do.
I'm making test batches.
Uh...
I see a skull icon.
This is the safe kind of skull icon.
What's a "safe kind" of skull icon?
Why don't you try a simpler recipe?
Just melt and mold it.
I'm not particularly good at cooking, either.
Oh, right.
I know someone who's a great cook.
Why don't you have them teach you?
We're a week into the third term.
We have a Sunday to work with.
Now's the time to buckle down.
So why isn't Itsuki here?!
"Please do begin!"
"And find out for us"...
What ever happened to that?!
There, there.
Calm down.
Where did she go, though?
Itsuki has that thing, remember?
It's that day for her.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Just say it!
He's asking straight-up.
You sure are insensitive, aren't you?
Well, it's hard to talk about, but...
What is it?
Is it more important than exams?
If it isn't, I'll kill her.
Well...
A girl has...
No, it's the day Mother died.
But wait, she was your mother, too.
To be accurate, it isn't today.
Mother passed away on August 14th.
So, like, the monthiversary?
Yeah.
She's devoted to visiting her grave
every month on the fourteenth.
Devoted, huh?
Itsuki, is that really the only reason?
Am I ever going to be like you, Mother?
Hey, I don't see other people here often.
Um...
Nice to meet you.
Teacher?
Sorry, you look so much like Teacher,
I thought you were her.
But thinking about it,
she's been dead for a long time.
That's not a nice thing to say
in front of her daughter, huh?
Forgive me.
There must be a reason
we bumped into each other here.
I'll buy you as much as you like, to show
my appreciation for your mother.
A-As much as I like?!
U-Um...
Miss Shimoda, are you my mother's...
I was her student.
I've lost count of how
many times she smacked me.
That's the thing.
Could you please tell me
what kind of person my mother was?
You don't remember?
It was only five years ago.
Surely you were old enough.
Yes, but...
I only know how my mother was at home.
I want to know what kind of
person she was as a teacher.
She was unfriendly. She never
tried to be nice to students.
I never saw her smile at school.
The students must have been
terrified of her, then.
Nope. Believe it or not, we weren't.
She could be as fierce
and expressionless as she pleased.
Hell, we loved her for it.
Teacher was just that damn super beautiful.
Super beautiful?
She even had a fan club.
The boys at school were utterly smitten.
Utterly smitten? Really?
Given how much you resemble her,
you're probably popular, too.
M-Me? Absolutely not!
Anyway, she was so pretty
that even I fell for her.
We delinquents revered her
for her expressionless wallops.
But there was always a certain
righteousness to it.
We'd eventually fall in love with
more than just her appearance.
All I remember of her for the entire year
was how she scolded us.
But without that year,
I wouldn't have wanted to be a teacher
or become a cram school instructor.
You've helped me come to
a decision, Miss Shimoda.
If I can follow in my mother's footsteps,
just like you did,
then my answer is obvious.
Just a second.
It's great that you admire your mother.
And there's nothing wrong with trying
to become like someone you admire.
That's what I did, too.
But you aren't just trying to
become your mother, are you?
There are plenty of other ways to do that.
That said, no one has the right to tell
you what what your dreams should be.
Go for it, if there's a reason
you want to become a teacher.
I...
Huh?
What are you doing all by yourself?
Nino.
I thought you had a study group
at school today.
Ichika made me come back.
Wait, are you the person
she was talking about?
Go get 'em, Miku.
Now she'll have no trouble
giving him V-Day chocolates.
As dense as he is,
even Futaro's sure to be surprised.
Why did I end up liking him?
What are you doing?
Are you all right?
Futaro?!
What was that?
What the heck are you doing?
Shoot.
Wh-Wh-Why...
Yotsuba said she forgot her reference
book at home, so I'm here to get it.
O-Oh, I think I threw that away the other day.
What?!
I'll go buy another one.
Hey!
Come with me.
What is this?!
It looks disgusting.
This is horrible.
Who's going to enjoy anything like this?
You're a double whammy of bad taste buds
and bad with your hands.
Just give up and buy some
chocolates from the store.
Shut up!
Shut up.
They say love is the best ingredient, though.
All that matters is that you made it.
Besides, it's a bit endearing
if it's not perfect.
This one's cute, like a bug!
Futaro won't eat my food lately.
I think I know why.
And I know I'm not good at it.
But I want to.
I want to make chocolates
that he can't resist.
I'd like you to teach me.
Please.
All the moisture's gone.
You're turning up the heat too much.
And you used dairy cream without
heating it up first, didn't you?
The texture's awful.
Jeez.
What a pain.
Get set up.
You're such a pain, you know that?
Found it. It's this one.
Boohoo...
Why is this happening?
It's pretty expensive.
Can you afford it?
U-Um...
Don't worry about it.
I'll go buy it.
Huh?
What about that book?
Oh, this is...
Is it actually something dirty?!
Hey!
I haven't decided to buy it yet.
Wow.
You want to become a good teacher, huh?
Sh-Shut up!
Don't be shy about it.
I'll buy it for you along
with the reference book.
I can buy it myself.
Don't worry about it.
We might really end up failing this time.
"This time"?
Huh? Don't you know?
It really was expensive.
I don't have much left in savings, too.
But if it'll make Futaro happy...
No, no!
This isn't a healthy relationship.
If we were to start going out,
I could totally see myself spoiling him
by spending on him all the time.
So I have to give up on him.
Yeah, that's the right call.
You bought it?
Yeah.
We're done shopping.
Let's go.
What happened to your hand?
I hit it back at the apartment.
It doesn't hurt that much, so don't worry.
You're so clumsy.
Be careful.
Okay.
I guess this side of him
is exactly why.
And he keeps doing this when I know
I shouldn't fall any harder for him!
Listen carefully, everyone.
The point here isn't to answer
with what the author is thinking.
It's to write what you, as the readers, feel.
Damn it, we've hit a wall.
Um...
What is it that I felt?
I did think we'd come to
this point eventually.
This is my limit as someone
who doesn't have the nous of a teacher.
I don't know what it is that they don't know!
I don't know how to teach them!
How cruel it is that our IQs must differ so!
I'm just guessing, but I have a
feeling he's thinking something rude.
I don't think we can focus anymore,
let alone answer these questions.
We've been studying nonstop for days.
I-I can still keep going!
"Cramming too much is counterproductive."
I see. They need an occasional reward.
Let's take the afternoon off.
Let's ride that one next!
Give me a second, Itsuki.
Huh? Where did Yotsuba go?
She says she's in the washroom
with a stomach ache.
Why doesn't she just say so?
Bathroom break for me, too.
Sure.
Catch up with us later.
Okay.
What?
Nothing.
Just how many laps are you doing?
I'm getting on.
Huh? That one's occupied.
Mind if I join you?
F-Feel free.
I thought I was doing a good job hiding.
How did I get found?
Because I saw that.
The ribbon was out of the bag!
You were studying here?
Yes.
I thought I could keep going,
since I have more stamina than the others.
Also, the secret is that I'm the
biggest dummy of the five of us.
We all know.
You should take a break.
We spent money to come to the amusement park.
No.
You don't have any idea how dumb I am.
Do you know why we transferred to this school?
Ichika told me.
You were about to flunk.
Our high school was what you
would call a prestigious one.
It wasn't unusual for people to be
held back a year if they failed an exam.
Naturally, we failed.
Don't make it sound natural!
We were given a chance to retake
the exams, so we all tried our best.
Don't tell me...
You were the only one who failed?
That's our Uesugi.
You get everything right.
Yotsuba was the only one who failed.
And yet they all transferred.
They all came along with me.
They never so much as frowned.
Is that from what you were taught
about staying together?
That's helped them through tough times,
but it's certainly shackling them as well.
So, please...
Let me study as much as I can.
I don't want to drag the others down anymore.
I told you, we're taking the day off.
That said, we have nothing to do for
the remaining half of the lap.
I'm bored. Let's study. Man-to-man.
Okay!
This is a good opportunity.
I'm going to make sure you understand
that Japanese passage from earlier.
Oh, that's okay.
I figured it out.
Let's see.
You did.
The other girls had so much trouble here.
Yotsuba!
Ack!
When you said man-to-man, you didn't
mean mouth-to-mouth, did you?
What happened on New Year's was an accident!
I'm beginning to see the light.
Your father's right.
If someone can help me,
I think we can make it work.
Could you, uh, dumb that down for me?
You'll teach Japanese with me.
Me?
I can't! I can't!
You can!
I've always known from your exam results that
you each have different areas of expertise.
Miku is good at Socials Studies.
Itsuki is good at Science.
And you, Yotsuba, are good at Japanese.
I am?
You don't have to do anything special.
Just say what's on your mind.
If you can do it, the other four can, too.
You're quintuplets.
I can be useful to everyone,
even if I'm stupid?
Sorry you're having to make up
for my failings as a teacher.
From now on, we'll all be
teachers and students together.
There's something an idiot like me can do?
Yeah, there's a job only you can do.
I'm not just going to drag everyone down?
That's right.
This time,
you'll be pulling everyone forward.
Okay.
I can handle this!
I'll make sure the others pass!
Hold it.
Don't forget that you're the biggest danger.
You really do come here every month.
Why are you here?
Your plan to have everyone be a tutor
is showing positive signs.
I realized you can learn some things better
by teaching than by being taught.
Are you telling me you don't need me anymore?
I'm appreciating what you taught us.
Thank you.
How does it feel to be thanked
by someone you taught?
Jeez, that's so patronizing.
I...
Wow, that makes so much sense.
Thanks, Itsuki!
I want to cherish that feeling.
Mother, I'm going to work
toward becoming a teacher.
It took me all night to make chocolates.
Miku.
Good morning.
You and Nino both stay in bed way too late.
Futaro.
You're here.
I wish you'd told me you were coming over.
I'm glad you're here, though.
Huh?
Where'd the chocolates go?
Oh, those?
I ate them, as always.
They were good.
Th-Thanks.
About those chocolates...
Miku, there's something
I should let you know.
You're number one.
Number one?
What do you mean by that?
The mock exam we did
the other day, of course!
You got the highest score!
Oh.
Cool.
I'm beginning to see some hope!
I'm going to keep trying.
Just watch me, Futaro.
So cold.
Ichika.
Long day at work, huh?
What are you doing?
How'd it go today?
Aren't you giving Futaro any chocolates?
Wh-What brings that up?
I mean, I'd feel bad for him if no one did.
I thought about buying him some.
But I figured it's all good
if you're going to.
What do you mean, "all good"?
Futaro doesn't see us as girls at all.
I've always known it, but to him,
we're all just students.
Miku...
That's why I made up my mind.
I'm going to pass this final exam.
And I'm going to get the
highest scores of all of us.
And if I can gain confidence and
graduate from being his student,
I'm going to really tell him
that I have feelings for him.
Th-That sounds good.
If that's your way of keeping
yourself disciplined...
I'm sure you can do it.
I'm not going to wait for you.
This is a race.
Yeah.
I can't be slacking off either, though.
So work hard.
Miku keeps changing.
I'm beat...
I should sleep and continue tomorrow.
These times aren't going to last forever.
A little more!
Just a little more.
Yotsuba!
How did the exams go?
Uesugi.
Thank you.
I feel vindicated for the first time.
Yotsuba!
You did it!
Congrats.
These are the highest scores I've ever gotten.
I just barely passed with
a total score of 184, though.
I scored 224 total.
I'm going to have to work on
the subjects that I nearly failed.
I got 238.
Wow!
I knew you could do it, Miku.
Ichika's here, too.
I'm here.
Miku.
I'm impressed.
I knew you had the most potential.
Futaro...
I...
What was your total score, Ichika?
Um...
240.
Which means...
You scored the highest, Ichika!
Oh, did I?
Yay.
Congratulations on passing your exams.
Let's celebrate.
Have as much as you like.
I'll deduct the bill from Uesugi's pay.
Oh, boss, you're so funny.
Thank you.
We're still missing one person, though.
The girl with the pigtails came
earlier and left this with me.
Also, she had a message for you.
Congratulations.
I have no more use for you now.
Yay!
We all made it through!
Hey, where are you going?
This is a celebration for everyone.
I'm going to go get Nino.
"Begin the Offensive."