I was dreaming...
There! Look!
We were just there! Kyoto Station!
Whoa, seriously?
Dreaming about the day we first met.
Our school trip was one disaster after another.
And then my mild cold turned into a full-blown flu.
It all ended with me going straight to the hospital.
And I get the feeling...
they came to pay me a visit.
Nah, no way.
Nino?
There's no one else here, is there?
Wh-What? This is my room.
What do you care?
Who do you think is paying for it?
It didn't have to be such a fancy private room.
The nurses are gossiping about how I might be the hospital director's bastard son.
What did you expect?
The girls thought you were going to die.
Your father was the one who paid for my hospital expenses too, wasn't he?
That's right.
Which basically means we paid for them.
Yikes. I didn't think anyone could be such a brat.
I never thought you of all people would come visit me, though.
I guess...
Shoot, I have to get going!
Don't you dare tell anyone about this, all right?
Uesugi, was Nino just here?
Yotsuba?
Hey.
Haven't seen you since the school trip.
How are you feeling?
And the rest of you...
Thank goodness.
I'm glad you're alive, at least.
Jeez.
Who ever asked you to come?
I definitely smell Nino.
Sniff, sniff...
Does she smell that bad?
Poor girl...
It's my perfume!
We weren't sure you were going to make it, at one point.
Your temperature was as high as a record-breaking summer day.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
You can call if you ever get lonely.
We'll come take care of you.
Thanks.
But I prefer being by myself.
Ow!
Wrong answer, Futaro.
Also, here.
Handouts from class while you were sick.
Good thing I finally got them to you.
So you're going to school, huh?
Yeah.
I might quit school.
You were never that committed, were you?
Come on, you're so mean.
I thought school was boring...
That I wouldn't have any problems quitting.
But I'm going to stay a little longer.
There's something I can't leave behind now.
You're aloof, insensitive, and mean.
So why...
does it have to be you?
Was there something you didn't like?
Huh?
I would've cooked for you if you'd asked me.
No, I just don't really have an appetite.
Oh.
Say "ahh".
Hey.
You'd better eat.
What are you doing?
Hey!
I found Nino!
What are you, a dog?!
Come on. Let's go.
L-Let me go!
Well, we'd better be going.
I hope you get better soon.
Huh?
What happened?
I feel a little better.
You're being discharged tomorrow, aren't you, Uesugi?
Yes.
Are you worried about your studies?
Well...
I'm doing fine,
but there are some idiots that I have to teach.
I see.
That concludes your examination.
S-Stop shoving!
Silence in the hospital, Nino.
I can't help it!
I was scared!
Those girls...
I guess I should thank them for coming to visit.
You're never going to get your ears pierced if you're afraid of needles.
Needles?
Uesugi.
What are you guys actually here for?
What for?
Vaccinations.
We always get vaccinated around this time every year.
But Itsuki and Nino keep running away.
I hate pain.
I'm glad we got to see Uesugi while we were at it, though.
You what...
Damn you all! You're going to get it!
You!
No shouting in the hospital!
You're sick! Rest up!
Uesugi...
I expect great things from you.
I feel like I've seen that man somewhere.
It was a long time ago.
But it's a scene that's etched firmly in my mind.
Right, that was...
Uesugi Futaro.
Bye-bye.
Why?
Why did I remember that?
Oh, it's just you, Itsuki.
Don't scare me like that.
I-I could say the same to you!
Yotsuba and the others have been looking for you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm here to ask you a question.
Tell me, why do you study?
Because that's my job as a student.
That is all.
What are you doing?
I'm going to keep staring at you until you tell me the truth.
Fine.
Want me to keep staring at you until you give up?
F-Fine.
We'll see who surrenders first.
Ah, young love.
So cute.
I'm not leaving until you tell me.
Give me a break.
Yes! I win!
That means you're getting the dare.
P-Please, anything but that!
I haven't been able to eat fish since last time!
I don't know...
Hey! Futaro!
We're in the train. Be quiet.
Come on, Takebayashi!
We're on a school trip!
Stop being a goody-two-shoes and join us!
Oh, fine, I will.
You should invite Sanada too, though.
It's the five of us in this group.
I'll pass.
Dude...
Arithmetic drills?
What are you, stupid?
Throw out all that useless junk!
For me, this is the only thing that matters.
Wow, that's awesome.
That's so cool.
I swiped it from my dad's work stuff.
Well, Takebayashi?
Do you want to take...
Are you all right?
Those two have known each other since they were little.
They live nearby, and their parents are close, too.
Their families have even gone on trips together.
And they're both class reps.
They look good together, huh?
Let's go, Futaro. Stop taking pictures.
R-Right.
Ow, ow, ow!
What's wrong?
My stomach suddenly started hurting.
Damn gut... Got me good.
I need to hit the bathroom.
I'll catch up later.
Throw out all that useless junk!
That's me.
Hey!
You took a picture of me just now, didn't you?
Huh? What do you want, lady?
You snuck a photo of me!
He snuck a photo of me!
I-I never did!
What's the matter?
This kid fell for my beauty! He snuck pictures of me!
Arrest him! Arrest him!
Did not!
There, there, calm down.
All right.
Let's check his camera, then.
I'm sorry, would you mind showing it to me?
Sure.
What's wrong?
No, I... um...
He's innocent.
I saw what happened.
This is an emergency!
An unidentified flying object has emerged over Japan!
We come from the planet of Shogi.
The most capable player in Japan shall play me for the fate of planet Earth.
And that's how my school trip ended.
What was that?!
That's the part I wanted to hear about! And you ended it so abruptly!
What happens to Earth?!
I never said I'd tell you.
I don't want to.
The only reason I did what you asked
was to thank you for coming the other day.
You don't sound that grateful.
But I can see that you've changed a great deal since then.
Meeting that girl changed you.
Whoa, lucky charms!
Let's buy some!
Why are you following me?
Go away!
Do you think I can change too?
I'd like you to help me change, if you could.
You're looking for someone, right?
I am too.
I can find them myself.
Go ask someone else.
It can't be anyone else.
We're both alone and lonely.
We have to stick together.
I need...
We need you.
I need you.
Hey, let's take a picture together.
Whoa, I never said you could touch it!
Don't look at me like that.
Is there any use in having me teach you?
Your average test score is a 29.6.
We'll make it work.
We'll do everything we can.
Look at this!
I dug up my old lucky charm.
You're resorting to prayer?
Oh yeah, that girl bought similar ones, too.
A ton of them.
Five of them.
Wait, where did you buy those?
These?
I don't remember if I bought them or if someone gave them to me.
I think they're from Kyoto, five years ago.
Does that mean...
Itsuki!
There you are.
We were looking all over for you.
Let's go, now that the five of us are here.
Itsuki, I'm going to do it!
And you're going down with me!
Hold on!
Five years ago...
In Kyoto...
It has to be a coincidence, right?
You just got out of the hospital. What do you want?
What's up?
Why did you want us all to wear our hair the same way?
Itsuki! Miku! Yotsuba! Nino! Ichika!
Nino! Miku! Itsuki! Yotsuba! Ichika!
You aren't tutoring us today?
What? You seem pretty enthusiastic, Nino.
I'm Nino.
So there you have it.
Without any hints, I don't know who's who.
You're like one of those recent idol groups!
I think that's just because you're disinterested.
In any case!
This happened just ten minutes ago.
Thanks for having me.
Not again...
Pervert!
But I pushed the doorbell!
I-Is this...
A zero in every subject.
And she went to the trouble of tearing her name off every sheet.
I couldn't tell who it was because she was in a bath towel,
but the culprit is among us.
Yotsuba, fess up.
You're just going to assume it was me?!
So that's why you had us all do our hair the same way.
How do you tell each other apart just by your faces?
Huh?
How?
Who else but Miku has such a bland face?
No one else but Nino has such an annoying face.
What do you mean, "bland"?
And what do you mean by "annoying"?
By "annoying", I mean annoying.
Uesugi, let me tell you something useful.
You're bland because you're bland!
Our mother taught us how to tell each other apart a long time ago.
Love will show you the way!
No wonder I couldn't tell.
Can we let our hair down now?
Why are you so serious today?
I smell shampoo...
That's kind of creepy.
Pervert!
That's it!
I need you to do something for me.
Call me a pervert.
You're a hopeless pervert.
That's not it. It didn't sound so hurtful.
You can tell us apart by our moles.
Perfect!
Where is it?
Show me!
Um...
I wouldn't mind showing you, Futaro.
No!
It's not going to help if you haven't seen the culprit's mole, is it?
That's true.
Futaro, it could be that the culprit isn't among us.
Explain.
Don't be shocked, okay?
We are sextuplets and have a secret sixth sister, Mutsumi!
What?!
Wh-Where is Mutsumi right now?!
She's in a secret room, unknown to any of us.
Forget this.
This isn't getting anywhere. Whatever.
Time for the last resort!
This problem set has questions from the earlier exams.
The one who does the worst is the culprit.
Why do we have to do this?
This is outrageous.
Futaro's kind of pushy today.
You're stuck now, Futaro.
I panicked and kicked you out in a hurry,
but that seems to have worked to my advantage.
I'd let my guard down on the quiz,
but I can do well if I try.
Sorry everyone, let's get this over with.
Wait...
My handwriting!
He's casually going to compare our handwriting.
Not bad, Futaro.
Close call.
I'm the only one who can dry my hair so quickly.
I wish I'd had some more time to get dressed, but...
There.
I'm done first.
You'll fail because you don't pay enough attention to girls.
So you're the culprit.
Huh?!
How?
I even changed my handwriting!
Here.
The way you write the letter "b".
I remembered you were the only one who writes it cursive.
I don't know you well enough to tell apart your faces,
but I've seen your handwriting more often than I'd like.
Y-
You got me!
So...
The rest of us finished, too.
Very well. Let me grade you.
Itsuki's "so" is the same as the culprit.
And Nino's "mon" radical...
Miku's "four".
Yotsuba's kanji suffix.
They're all the same as the culprit's!
Each one of you failed a quiz!
Busted.
What have you done, Ichika?!
You were supposed to hide them before he got here!
Sorry.
I'm stuck in hospital for a while,
and this is what happens?
I don't know if you're all...
Uesugi.
The reason you were trying so hard to tell us apart...
It has something to do with that girl from five years ago you mentioned, right?
You think it's one of us, don't you?
Yeah.
What's the point in buying all of those?
This is to make me try five times harder.
I'm going to become an example for the others.
Raise your hand if you met me a long time ago.
Where'd that come from?
What are you talking about?
Figures.
There's no way that girl was one of you idiots.
H-How dare you call us idiots?!
I'm not wrong, am I?
I can't believe you've been hiding the exams you bombed.
We're spending all day today on review.
Itsuki...
Was that on purpose?
I don't care about you anymore, Futaro.
S-Sorry!
It looks like you need to do some studying first, Uesugi.
Though now that I take a good look,
quintuplets can be quite different.
Still, for now,
I don't think I'm going to be able to tell them apart without their handwriting.
"Seven Goodbyes, Part 1."