Ichika likes you.
What do you want?
Must be rough, eh, Uesugi?
Tutoring the Nakanos.
How did you know about that?
My dad's the president of this high school.
My family has a very close
relationship with Mr. Nakano.
Damn elite cabals.
I can't imagine you'd have the time
to be tutoring right now, though.
Now that you've fallen from
the top of our grade,
there've been discussions
that I ought to take over.
I've finally taken the top position
in our grade from you!
Yes!
I win! I win!
Yes! Oh, yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Uesugi,
our long-standing rivalry has come to an end!
It began two years ago, when I was pursuing
the top of the grade, and you appeared...
Wait, who are you?
Y'know, I'm Takeda Yusuke. I've been
on your heels in grades this whole time.
Never heard of you.
I've only ever gotten full marks. I've never
thought about anyone second or below.
Second or below?!
All right.
Let's begin our study session.
Um...
Is Takeda joining us?
Why are you following me?
You don't have time to be doing this, do you?
There's something more important
for you to be doing.
What are you talking about?
To be frank,
these girls are holding you back.
Holding him back?!
For him to quit tutoring would be
in his best interest, above all else.
It's your fault.
You turned him into a mediocre man.
I'd appreciate if you'd free him already.
You're right.
But until last summer, or rather,
if I hadn't taken this job,
I would have failed to
even be a mediocre man.
I'd thought I knew it all just from
memorizing textbooks cover to cover.
I never knew that there were
such idiots in the world.
That I was as much of an idiot as I am.
I'm going to stick with them
for as long as they want.
Futaro.
If you insist, I'd like to see
you prove it with results.
If you don't make it in, say, the top one
hundred of the coming national mock exams,
I'll have you accept my conditions.
Top hundred?
Forget about it.
Top ten.
I'm going to continue tutoring them
and make it into the top ten
of the national mock exams.
And I'm going to prove that
they aren't holding me back.
Uesugi!
You're going big.
You don't stand a chance.
Especially if you're teaching
the five of them at the same time.
Sorry, I'm going to go get some fresh air.
I need to get their grades up
so they can graduate.
I'd like to focus on my own mock exam, but...
No, I need to make both happen.
They aren't holding me back.
Futaro.
Miku.
Oh, I am very serious.
About the day after tomorrow...
About the day before yesterday...
Go ahead.
You go.
I...
What are you guys talking about?
Wh-What does it matter?
Do you think Futaro will be okay?
He'll be fine.
All we can do is lighten his
burden as much as we can.
So let's forget about the
birthday thing for now.
Okay.
I can't regret what I did.
This is how I decided I was going to fight.
I've put the brakes on the others,
so this is my chance!
I'm going to be the only
one giving him a gift.
I can't be having second thoughts now.
I spent too long choosing, and now I'm late.
Nino.
What's that?
Oh, these?
Stress-relieving candles.
His birthday's almost here.
Oh, shoot.
I was supposed to keep it
a secret until the day of.
Didn't you see my message last night?
Oh, that?
I did, but I want to
give him a gift, so I will.
Hang on, does that mean I'm the
only one giving him a gift?
It'll work even better, then.
I forgot.
Nino's brakes are busted!
So?
Huh? So what?
You have a gift for him too, don't you?
We're going to have to make one thing clear.
I asked you to stop Dad on the
last day of our spring break vacation.
And yet, he arrived where
we were supposed to meet up.
Do you have an explanation?
We all have different tastes
for quintuplets, right?
Yeah, and that always makes
doing the cooking a real pain.
Nino, do you like Futaro?
I love him.
So do I.
Why does this have to be
the one thing we agree on?
Sorry, Nino, but I don't plan
on letting you have him.
How condescending, just because
you're technically the oldest sister.
Who even gives a guy aromatherapy candles?
What? Your gift card's pretty tacky, too!
Why?
He can use it to buy what he really wants!
You scared me.
I thought Uesugi came back.
What are you making, Yotsuba?
One crane of thousand.
I thought we could make them
for him to help his grades.
Isn't that something you give to sick people?
I've heard they do bring good luck.
Uesugi seems kind of tired.
He never admits it,
but tutoring us while he's also
studying himself is a huge burden,
so I want him to at least stay healthy.
Done!
Didn't we agree not to do gifts, though?
Sorry!
I didn't mean it that way!
Y-Yotsuba, we're in the library.
You don't have to beat yourself up over it!
I hate myself!
I feel like I'm cheating!
I'm a horrible human being
for breaking our agreement!
Um...
Sorry.
These are couples tickets for the gym.
I thought we could train together.
I asked for a partial advance
on my pay so I could afford them.
Sorry for trying to get ahead.
We sure are quintuplets.
Let's do this, then.
It'll get in the way of his studying if we
give him anything before the mock exams.
So let's all give him our gifts after.
Okay!
That sounds good.
H-Hey!
Who said you could decide?
Are you even okay with that?
You guys don't get him.
Even if we all give him our gifts,
he's going to like mine the best.
So nothing on his actual birthday, then?
I know!
How about this?
Studying so late?
You must be having a rough time.
This is for you.
Itsuki.
What do you mean?
This isn't rough.
Who do you think I am?
I visited a cram school instructor
named Miss Shimoda the other day.
I don't know if it counts as work,
but I'm going to aim to improve my academic
capabilities while I assist Miss Shimoda.
Am I not good enough?
Please don't get upset.
This isn't about you.
I just wanted to do a job that
I could make part of myself.
For the sake of my dream past the
mock exams and past graduation,
I wanted to get a look
at education in action.
I can never predict you guys.
Ever since the new term, Yotsuba,
Nino, Ichika, and even Miku...
Has something happened?
I'll tell you someday.
How long has it been?
Oh, yeah, that was today.
I should go home.
Five cranes?
What's this?
I guess I'm not alone.
They're working hard, too.
I have to keep up.
We've received the results of the national
mock exam from several days ago.
Though their grades vary, all of them have
made considerable progress since last year.
I was eighth nationally.
And Uesugi...
You got me.
Third nationally?
I have to tip my hat to you, Uesugi.
Um...
This is a bakery, right?
Not a rock shop?
W-Well, Nakano just started working here.
It looks dead.
I don't get it.
I'm having her follow the instructions.
She has some mysterious
ability to screw it up.
Maybe I'm not cut out for this.
H-Have confidence!
I think it's becoming more
food-like than before.
Keep it up!
Okay.
It's bread!
Did you really make this, Miku?
Yup.
We can't quite sell this yet.
I'm glad you got this far, though, Miku.
Thank you, manager.
Let's have Uesugi try this.
I bet he'll be surprised.
It's not that good yet.
Did you say you were aiming
for the school trip?
Yes.
Lunch on the first day is
supposed to be up to us.
"In raiding and plundering be like fire."
I'm going to give him my
best one when we're there.
I see!
I'm sure he'll love it.
There's one more problem, though.
We might not be able to spend lunch
together if we aren't in the same group.
I want to tour Kyoto with
him more than anything.
Miku...
Leave this to me!
With the national mock exams over,
I'd like to discuss the school trip.
We'll be forming groups for our activities.
Each group can have up to five people.
Let's see...
Where is Uesugi?
There!
Hey! Uesugi—
Yotsuba.
Over here.
What's up, Ichika?
I can't wait for the school trip, can you?
People are having trouble with
forming groups of five or less...
but it's perfect for us, huh?
Good thing we're quintuplets, huh?
But what about Futaro?
He's a third-year, and he doesn't
seem to have any friends.
I'm worried about him.
Um... In that case...
All right.
We should make a sacrifice for him.
Ichika?
You, me, and Futaro should form a group.
Is that okay?
Huh? Ichika!
Sorry, I got a call.
Okay, take care of it!
Jeez, bro.
You're glued to your desk
again on your day off.
What else am I supposed to do
on my precious day off?
Oh, right, I have to thank you
for the birthday party.
Is it a gift?!
What is it?
No thanks.
You don't need to thank me.
You should be thanking Yotsuba.
Why would you bring up Yotsuba?
I knew you'd forget!
Didn't she help you at school camp?
I told you, you need to give her
something in return.
It's a new school year.
I can't believe you'd just left it.
That's what's wrong with you!
Huh? A gift for me?
From you?
My budget is 1,000... 1,500 yen.
Is that why you showed up
here out of nowhere?
It's so like you to ask, though.
Shouldn't you make it a
surprise or something?
I'm tired of giving gifts
that people don't want.
Just tell me what you want.
Let's see...
I know a good place to go.
This is going to be a fun day!
You sure?
So far, we're just walking.
That's why it's fun.
This is a date.
Wh-Why don't we go for lunch first?
Lunch, huh? I'm up for anything.
This restaurant is Itsuki's favorite.
There's no way we're going
to eat here for under 1,500 yen.
This is the spa Miku was a member at.
No way!
The movie Ichika's in.
Ooh.
Good thing she gave me tickets.
That wouldn't make it a gift from me.
Finally, I found it!
I've been looking for this.
Clothes, huh?
I'll buy you that, then.
I wouldn't mind going a little over budget.
Yay!
Nino's been wanting this.
I bet she'll be happy.
Hang on a second.
Yotsuba, what is it that you want?
The restaurant, the spa,
the theater, shopping...
None of it was about you.
Um, just give me a second.
I'm going to think about it.
Uh...
Uesugi, what is it that I want?
Where has Yotsuba gone?
We were supposed to clean up
around the house today.
Itsuki, do you recognize this box?
Oh, that's my stuff.
I packed up some clothes that
I don't think I'll be wearing.
You should throw it out if you don't need it.
Not that I can talk.
Itsuki, you dropped something.
This is from Kyoto.
I see.
Huh...
I'm surprised you know a place like this.
I come to this park often.
I hop on the swing when I'm a bit bummed.
I-I guess this is nothing fancy, though.
Let's go somewhere nicer.
It's been a while, but I've still got it.
Uesugi?
Are you impressed, Yotsuba?
Jeez, you're like a child.
Besides, that's not that impressive.
I'll show you how it's done. Watch this.
See? How's that!
I can go even higher!
I like this view you get
when you swing full force.
It's not exactly a million-dollar nightscape,
but when I imagine that there's a home—
a family—for every light...
I feel warm inside.
And then...
I beat my old record!
Can you come this far, Uesugi?
Of course I...
U-Uesugi!
Did you see that?!
What just happened?!
What is it that you want?
What on earth are you doing?
Anyway, it's late. Let's go home.
Huh? Okay.
Man, I never got her anything.
Do I have anything?
I-If this will do...
That's so you, Uesugi.
Thank you.
But I already got what I wanted.
You did?
Yes.
Okay, then.
Are you sure?
Let's come back again.
With everyone, next time.
This is for middle schoolers!
Hey, you're all here today.
Well, let's start studying.
But first, I want to talk
about the school trip.
Futaro, have you chosen who
you're going to go with?
I...
Wait!
Yotsuba said she has something to say.
U-Um...
I...
Right?
What?
Hurry up.
U-Um, well...
Miku and Ichika can come with...
But Itsuki and Nino...
We sisters have to stay together.
Oh, I know!
Let's just all be in the same group!
You, too, Uesugi!
Wha?
That would be ideal, but we can
only have up to five per group.
I meant everyone besides me.
That solves everything.
That's a bit much.
I can't have that, Yotsuba.
Is there a problem?
There is.
A huge one.
Yeah.
The problem is that no one wants that.
At the very least, I don't.
How about this, then?
Fu and I form a group by ourselves.
"Fu"?
I don't know what Yotsuba was about to say,
but that's been my plan all along.
I'm going with who I like.
You don't get to say no.
U-Uh, Nino, I never...
Stay out of this, Fu.
"Fu"...
I-I...
If you have something to say, say it now.
It's settled.
No, it's not!
Hear me out!
I told you to stay quiet!
Just be grateful that you
get to go on a date with me!
I already made a group with
some guys from our class.
Sorry.
Who's going to be the group leader?
You mustn't forget about me.
Why does it have to be this way?
I thought those five would make a group.
They must be really tight-knit,
to go as sisters.
So it's the same as always.
I'm glad Futaro has some friends now.
This is so awkward!
"Sisters War: Part 1."