Let's do this, then.
I'll hear you guys out.
Did she not hear that?
Thank you!
Dude! Why are you on this side?!
It's a mixed bath. There's no issue here.
I'm right here!
What are you talking about?
We're friends. This is perfectly normal.
Maybe not.
I'm sorry. I'd appreciate
if you'd forget that.
There's something I'm counting on you to do.
Take care of it.
Father.
May I talk to you for a bit?
What is it?
Well...
Okay.
Once I'm past here, the rest is easy.
I just need to talk to the
rest of them, one at a time.
That could very well help me
figure out who the fake Itsuki is.
I doubt they have anything
serious on their minds, anyway.
Ichika, Nino, Miku, Yotsuba...
Just you wait...
I'm coming for you!
A forest of Itsukis!
Why are you all Itsuki?
Come on, Futaro,
learn to knock first.
We scared him.
What we're doing...
This is a good opportunity.
I wanted to try this on you again anyway.
Do you remember the quintuplets game?
Why don't you try guessing who's who?
Introduce myself? Okay.
I'm Nakano Itsuki.
Born May 5th.
17 years old, blood type A.
What I like?
I definitely feel happy
when I'm having good food.
Uesugi, you mustn't ask
such questions of a girl!
Damn it, I can't tell them apart at all.
Um... If you don't have any more questions...
Why are you all impersonating Itsuki?
Well...
It's a long story, but...
Um....
This Itsuki might be...
The five of us quintuplets
have always looked identical,
and everyone could see
that we were tight-knit.
Grandpa was happy to see it, too.
But one day, I tried dressing up
differently from everyone else.
Oh?
How did you dress up?
The same-bunny ear ribbon that I wear...
You're Yotsuba!
I-I have no idea what you're talking about!
Given how she's the worst liar, I figured
she'd be easy to find, but not that easy.
L-Let Itsuki take over from here.
Fine.
Finish your story.
Grandpa became worried when he saw that
the five of us weren't the same anymore.
He thought we might have had a falling out.
One day, he collapsed.
And since then, we've decided to
look the same when we're around him.
And after some discussion,
we decided we'd be Itsuki.
So once spring break started
and we decided we'd be coming here,
I've been worried that I might
not be able to pull off the look.
Is that what's been bugging you
this whole time?
Everyone seemed to be having fun,
so I didn't want to bring it up.
You do all that for that scary old man?
You're good people.
No.
He's a very kind man.
I love him.
It might be a stupid worry to me,
but it's serious for them.
Well, can you tell us apart,
now that you've talked to us?
Yeah.
Huh?
Which one's the fourth Itsuki?
I had it a second ago!
I'm disappointed.
You really can't, huh?
Wait! One more try!
Grandpa.
Morning.
Huh?
He seems worried about something.
Don't worry.
We're all still the same, best buddies.
That was close.
I was afraid it was their dad,
but this is fine.
If Fake Itsuki is here, one of them
might have a bruise from last night.
H-Hey...
N-No.
What do you think you're doing?!
Found it!
This is the fake Itsuki!
Want to go to the main hall?
Hey, Ichika.
Want to go take a morning bath?
Sure.
That wasn't entirely fruitless.
But why?
They passed the term finals.
Things were going well.
May I have a word with you?
Um...
Yotsuba?
Bzzt.
Here's a hint.
Nino?
Hint number two.
Oh, Ichika!
Got it!
It's Itsuki herself!
You're doing this on purpose.
I legit can't figure it out.
Are you itchy anywhere?
Sheesh.
You don't have to do that.
So why is it me this time?
Y'know, you get it a lot, don't you?
Getting asked out and stuff.
I can't talk to the other girls about it.
There's someone I like.
Where is everyone?
I need grub.
I need food!
That's not quite right.
I'm in dire need of food!
Yup, that's how Itsuki would say it.
S-So we went to buy curtains,
but all of us had differing tastes.
Uesugi...
How long do I need to be here for?
We all chose different curtains,
and things got kind of ugly at one point.
I haven't even had breakfast yet.
I am in dire need of some food!
You must have been surprised
when you saw Dad with us.
Yeah.
I accidentally wrote our old address
when I signed up for the giveaway with you.
Although we all got to be
here together as a result.
It's Miku.
I could never tell from how she looks.
All you need is love!
Don't give up!
Observe her carefully!
Love all the way!
Itsuki says there's something
bothering Miku, too.
I think I've got a rough idea of what it is,
and it happened last month.
Don't tell me, what's bothering Miku is...
I'm disappointed in myself.
Since when did I bother thinking
about this kind of thing?
I feel a creepy stare on me.
I give up.
Please stop being mean and tell me.
That's against the rules.
Try a little harder.
I want you to get it right, too, Futaro.
At least show me your legs, then.
Wait, what? Why?
Grandpa.
What?
I saw you trying to lay your hands
on my granddaughter again.
I haven't done anything today.
Miku, has he done anything to you?
H-He hasn't.
That old man figured out
she's Miku just by looking at her.
Miku, I'll catch up later.
Grandpa!
I mean, Master!
I have a request!
I wanted to ask for relationship advice.
The way I met him was the worst.
But I went on to realize that I love him.
Nino, please...
Don't say any more.
He's...
No!
I can't say it!
I already know, though.
I told him how I felt just the other day.
But I don't know if I did the right thing.
So I wanted to ask...
When someone confesses to you,
do you think about them more?
If I'm just speaking from experience...
Sorry, I don't think it
worked out that way for me.
I have feelings for Futaro, too.
So please, let me keep things
the way they are for now.
Oh, so just telling him
how I feel isn't enough?
Huh?
No, I mean...
You said it was horrible
the way you met him, right?
Are you sure you love him?
He appeared as a force of destruction
against something that was dear to me.
But one night, I mistook him for
my Prince Charming and fell in love.
And soon, I came to realize
that what I rejected was his role
and not him as a person.
Once I realized that he was my prince,
I couldn't control myself anymore.
What...
And you fell in love, just like that?
Don't you think that's too self-centered?
You're right.
I creep myself out too, honestly.
I don't intend to give up, though.
I mean, this is my love.
What's the point if it doesn't make me happy?
Wh-What if there's someone else
who likes the same guy?
What if that person cares about him
way more than you do?
Well, I guess...
I'd feel bad, but I'd walk over them
to get with him, if I had to.
I think that's how I'd feel.
Sh-She's unstoppable.
She's a runaway train of love!
She won't even listen to me!
I thought she wanted advice!
I'm glad I talked to you.
I guess a confession isn't enough.
What are you going to do?!
I'll take his hand.
No, I'll hug him.
And if he still doesn't take the hint,
I'll kiss him.
Th-That's not a good idea!
You shouldn't kiss him out of nowhere!
You're right.
Now that you mention it...
He'll be turned off if I'm bad at it.
Have you done any kiss scenes yet?!
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
Come on, we're sisters!
It's wrong because we're sisters!
I'm going to sneak out at night to see him.
Dad's going to be a problem when I do.
So I need you to keep an
eye on him for me, Ichika.
Nino's going to meet up with Futaro.
And she might even kiss him.
I can't stop her anymore.
She's not a coward like I am.
She doesn't care what anyone thinks.
She loves him with everything she has.
I don't even stand a chance.
I don't have the right.
Washroom...
Ichika.
What's wrong?
Ichika...
Don't cry.
I know, it's been a while.
Let's go to our secret place.
Dad.
He'd never expect us to be up here.
What do I do?
I'm supposed to stop him for Nino.
Um...
Ichika.
I don't know what's going on, but...
But...
It still gets chilly at night.
You shouldn't have come out
so lightly dressed.
Your nose is running.
I-I can handle it myself!
You're always such a child.
Thanks.
You're trying to cheer me up, right?
I'm all right, though.
I have to go after Dad.
Wait.
Are you trying to be tough?
I'm worried.
Sorry if I'm just overthinking it.
Where has everyone gone?
What if they're with Futaro?
There's no reason to see him
so late at night.
Or maybe there is.
Miku.
Just waiting here won't help.
Why don't we go to the baths?
I've been thinking about
the old days since we got here.
Like how Grandpa used to be really scary.
Or how Mom scolded us all
the time for our mischief.
You've always been rambunctious.
Oh, come on.
You were the one who got in the most trouble.
W-Was I?
Don't tell me you forgot.
Even among us identical twins,
you were the big bully figure.
I lost count of the number of times
you stole my snacks.
S-Sorry.
The stickers I'd been collecting
were on your backpack.
I'm sorry.
And I saw people who I tried to be friends
with talking to you the next day.
I used to do that as a kid?
I-I guess I've grown up since then.
It's so weird.
I've stayed a kid this whole time.
How come you were able to grow up?
That's because...
I saw Itsuki-chan in so much pain after Mom died.
I had no choice.
I had to be the older sister.
Yeah. I'm glad you're my older sister.
I've been wanting to say this.
As a kid, you were the mean bully, always
wanting to take things from other people.
But you were the leader of us sisters.
I've always thought of you
as our big sis.
So...
Wait, what was I trying to say?
I don't want you to hold back.
I want you to do what
you want to do, I guess.
What I want to do?
I wanted these times to go on forever.
I always wanted to be here
in this comfort zone.
But the truth is...
I didn't want anyone else to take him.
Wait... what?
I was actually cold, too.
You're taking it back
after you lent it to me?!
Okay, let's go back inside.
Okay.
So, didn't you have to go see Dad?
Nah.
I'm good now.
Huh?
What are you doing here?
Um...
Itsuki.
Miku.
That's what I was about to say!
You said it first!
I was about to say it!
Um, what are you...
Just a little more!
Just give me a little longer!
Your grandpa's about to teach me!
Hold up!
I don't believe it.
He has no intention of
figuring it out himself.
What can he do?
There's no way he can learn to
tell us apart after just half a year.
Please, Grandpa, tell me already.
Isn't there a trick or something
to telling them apart?
Love.
You can tell them apart if you have love.
So he's the one who started it!
Over a long time, you learn to identify
their mannerisms, voice, subtle habits...
That is tantamount to love.
You said you wanted to
tell my grandkids apart.
There is no silver bullet.
Why do you want to tell my grandkids apart?
What is it you want to accomplish
by being able to tell them apart?
Do you have the commitment
to face them in good faith?
Can I assume you're the Itsuki
I talked to on the first night?
Yes.
I am...
Hold it.
I never did figure out how to win
the quintuplet game.
Victory is yours.
But I don't like being a loser.
I want a rematch.
I'm going to figure you out myself,
even if I get no one else.
That's my show of commitment
to facing you sisters in good faith.
Itsuki has told you what's going on, correct?
Yes.
First, Yotsuba's problem
is with this trip itself.
Therefore, at the end of today,
she no longer has to worry.
And you aren't Yotsuba.
She isn't as perfect an impersonator as you.
Correct.
Next, Nino...
She wasn't quite perfect.
She forgot to remove her pedicure.
Please stop, Futaro.
This is pointless.
That leg...
It was you, Miku?
Oh.
My bruise never went away.
Miku...
You were always the most cooperative.
Why are you trying to end your
relationship with Uesugi?
I have to apologize to you first.
I was in a panic because Grandpa was there.
No, that's an excuse, too.
I couldn't tell him as myself.
I love Futaro, and yet...
You have a crush on Uesugi?!
My goodness!
Everyone's going to be
shocked when they hear!
I'm pretty sure everyone knows.
But are you sure?
We're technically students and teacher.
That's why.
He and I are teacher and student.
If this goes on, our relationship
will never change.
I understand how you feel.
So I have a request...
Please meet Uesugi one last time.
Therefore, you aren't Nino, either.
Correct.
Then what is it that's on Nino's mind?
That's probably...
Well... That's one thing I shouldn't say.
All right.
I'll avoid asking.
You're either Ichika or Miku.
If I think of her as Ichika,
she looks like Ichika.
But that goes for Miku, too.
Nope. I don't know.
I give up.
Of course.
What was I expecting?
Could you call her for me?
Her?
Y'know, her.
Her name is...
Itsu...
Oh, that's what he's doing.
Itsuki-chan?
You fell for it!
Ichika's the only one who
calls her Itsuki-chan!
Which means you're Ichika!
You got me good.
Sheesh, you made me waste so much time.
I figured it'd be you, since I couldn't
figure out what was bothering you.
Wow.
Is it about work?
I heard it's gotten busy.
Something like that.
Well, I have to get ready for the trip home.
See you.
Over a long time, you learn to identify
their mannerisms, voice, subtle habits...
This is the only way I can tell them apart.
But that's fine.
That solves everything.
Fake Itsuki, you are...
That is tantamount to love.
Are you Miku?
Why?
I said I was Ichika.
Uh, sorry.
I might be imagining it, but for a second,
you looked like Miku.
Bingo!
Seriously?
Can I ask you something?
You seemed to have a hunch
about what was bugging me.
If I wasn't Fake Itsuki,
what would you have thought it was?
It's an embarrassing thought,
now that I know I was wrong...
I'll tell you, so don't laugh.
I thought you were mad because I didn't
give you anything in return after V-Day.
I said not to laugh!
Why did you want me to quit, anyway?
Actually, forget that.
What?
Futaro's a teacher.
I'm his student.
That won't change.
Thank you for guessing correctly.
Bye-bye.
See you.
My grandkids are all I have to live for,
now that I've lost Rena.
Tell my grandkids to stay true to themselves.
Over a long time, you learn to identify
their mannerisms, voice, subtle habits...
That is tantamount to love.
If that's true, then the reason
I knew it was Miku...
In any case, it's true that
I could tell them apart.
"Welcome to Class 3-1."