Moshimo kimi igai no
If I were to fall for someone else
Betsu no hito ni koishiteitara
And my head swirled with thoughts of them instead of you
Onaji you ni kurushikatta no?
Do you think this aching in my heart would still be there?
Iie chigau yo
No, don't even answer!
Hajimari mo shinakatta yo
'Cuz no matter what, it's just you that I want!
Mezamete sugu ni kangaeteru
From the moment that I wake, you're right there in my head
Jibun janakute ne kimi no koto
I don't even give myself a single thought at all!
Okashii kurai ippai na no
Head spinning off the rails, as if I've lost my mind
Bureeki nante mou nai
There's no stopping it now! And that's just fine!
Nee hanareteru toki kono kokoro wa
From the instant that we part, I long to see your face again
Aitai kimochi de mae wo muku nda
These feelings in my heart reach out no matter the distance
(massugu)
(straight to you)
Shinjiteru mayoi no nai koe de
With not even a moment of doubt, I'll put my faith in you
Watashi wo mitsukedashitekuretakara
How could I not, when you are the one
who showed me my true self?
(arigatou)
(thank you so much)
"Suki" jibun ni mo omoeru you ni naritai
And now, after all this time, I've finally grown to love myself